<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wolfpack Alliance</title>
    <description>Legendary Alliance in PixelStarships - a Mobile Sci-Fi MMO Game</description>
    <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wolfpackpss.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 23:39:28 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 23:39:28 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;13 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;A Farewell&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-246&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #246.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was another goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx summoned us together to announce the parting. Those of us who knew her best. Those of us who would miss her most. Those of us who would feel her absence, no longer flying by our side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl had gone on to Lost Eden.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a galaxy of partings. A captain’s term was not long. A couple months at most. A blazing fiery start full of firepower and fervent friendships sharing a common cause. And then they were gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their ships standing as an empty masoleum of the great war power they had once commanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walking away to disappear in the distant horizon. Good friends departed. Forgotten, but for the glories and friendships they left behind. Those who would remember them most.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl, you only shared one story with me. I was not able to say goodbye. I will do my best to tell your story well:&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;********&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red alarms were flashing across the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl pushed herself up off the console. The display was smashed. She touched her brow. There was a slight cut where her head hit the console. Nothing serious. It could wait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She remembered feeling an internal explosion rupture the ship. Then the shields dropped and they took a volley of enemy fire at full impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She stood and checked on her crew.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cara was slumped against the systems monitor. Test girl grabbed her by the collar and pulled her back in the chair. Her eyes opened slowly with difficulty and then focused on Test girl’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl patted her on the chest, “Cara, bring up the systems and get me a damage report immediately. I need to know what hit us and took out our shields.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessica was on the floor. The weapons display was destroyed. Jessica took the brunt of it. Test girl didn’t have much hope, but she checked her pulse. Nothing. She squeezed Jessica’s arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weapons would have to be controlled individually at each of the weapon rooms. She had trained her crew for this. They were good crew. They wouldn’t fail her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, systems report the shield generator was destroyed while the shields were still up. Without the generator, the shields dropped immediately.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generator was destroyed while the shields were up? It couldn’t have been hit by enemy fire. Weapons wouldn’t have gotten through the shields. It must have come from the inside.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cara, patch me through to the shield room.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bridge doors opened and a Trooper walked in. Test girl’s hand dropped to her blaster, then realized it was her Trooper. He looked around bewildered at the disarray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, the comms are destroyed. I can’t reach them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frak. She looked at her Trooper. She only had one runner. She would have to make the message count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cara, fix the communications. I need to be able to talk to my ship. Trooper, head to the teleporter room. Tell Zhang Fei to board the enemy ship and dismantle their shields.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was their only shot. Even the playing field and bring themselves back into the fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trooper looked at her, “Sir, enemy shield generators are heavily guarded. If you send Zhang Fei in there, they’ll kill him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl gave her Trooper a hard look. One crew for many. This was battle. She did not like to be reminded of the lives she risked. Nor would she repeat an order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She gave her Trooper a hard look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes sir! I will relay your order,” Trooper stood at attention and saluted, then rushed out the door.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl rested her knuckles against the cracked display and leaned against the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She would bring her ship through this. She had to. The lives of her crew depended on her. This new strategm was powerful. One they could use against their enemies. She must relay it to Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;********&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a small vigil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx, WarWolff, Sumara, Caxy, Deathlord291, Machiel, Hyten, Seq and I. Standing together on the captain’s bridge of WarWolff’s great warship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We looked out the observation window. Seeing Test girl’s proud craft in all its glory. Her last flight into Lost Eden. We watched quietly as her ship flew away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx put his hand against the glass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara wrapped her arms around his and I placed a hand on his shoulder. Deathlord291 and Machiel bowed their heads. Hyten and Seq lit a candle for their departing friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a tear in WarWolff’s eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only Caxy remained stoic. It was another goodbye. He had said so many before.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodbye, Test girl. May your journey find you happiness and new friendships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodbye, old friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist013_Testgirl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist013_Testgirl&quot; title=&quot;Test girl in Lost Eden&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/08/history-of-the-pack-a-farewell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/08/history-of-the-pack-a-farewell.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;12 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Book Of Secrets, pt. 2&amp;#58; The Curse&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-244&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #244.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had been searching for it for years. Finally, here at last. In an unmarked tomb. Buried beneath the S.Q.U.I.D. empire. He had found it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It spoke of battle. It promised of victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The secrets it held. The knowledge it could reveal. No enemy could withstand him. There was nothing he could not do with the book in his grasp.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel brushed the back of his hand across his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He looked around the room one more time. The cold concrete walls. His Troopers standing at the entrance. The stone pedestal. The thick starlight pouring down through the ceiling. The Book Of Secrets bathed in light atop the slab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could feel the tension in the air. Himself holding his breath. The excitement. The suspense. Everything he had been pursuing, bringing him to stand here at this one moment in time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel reached out and dipped his fingers in the circle of light. It was like touching a waterfall. He turned his palm upward into the starlight, as it glimmered caressingly around his hand. Like jets of warm water. Splashing through his fingers and down his wrist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It felt of pure energy. Joy. Laughter. Rejuvenation. He couldn’t help but smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an end to his many years of struggle and pursuit. This rich beautiful starlight running through his fingers. His trophy before him. The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would finally lay claim to the treasure for which he had been searching for so long. Machiel turned his hand over and touched its pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circle was broken.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The starlight sucked up into the ceiling. Swallowing the room in darkness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down the hall, in the blacks of the shadows, there was a deep rumbling. A moist coolness oozed into the room from the passageway. Riding on the backs of the waves of a low billowing fog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Troopers backed away from the entrance with their blasters raised. Machiel stepped down from the pedestal, leaving the book behind, and drew his electro-sword. Slowly they converged together in the center of the room. Standing back-to-back. Huddling beneath what little light still came through the ceiling overhead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phosphorescent shapes began to move through the fog. Swimming around the edges. Splashing up and smearing down the walls. Leaving green streaks trailing behind them on the porous concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menacing, they slowly began circling. Easing towards the center of the room. Circling around Machiel and the Troopers. Weaving between their legs. Sliding up their knees. Finding the soft joints in their armor and oozing in cool fingers.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the Troopers panicked and started firing wildly at the floor and walls. The shots did nothing. It was all Machiel and the other Trooper could do to restrain him. A single bad ricochet in this confined space could kill any one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slowly, the fog and phantasms began pouring up the pedestal and into the book. Dark billows of fog and green phosphorescence oozing between the letters. Seeping into the pages. Staining its bamboo darkly like spilled watercolor.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the last of the fog swept past them and into the book, the cover closed on its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tomb became eerily silent. More frightening than anything they had just witnessed. They were afraid to move lest they disturb the peace of any more otherworldly beings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel carefully walked back to the pedestal, stepping lightly on the balls of his feet. He looked down uncertainly at the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be a shame to not take it with them. After all the years of searching, despite what they had just seen. There must still be some good in its pages worth salvaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He reached out a hand, then paused. Frowning again uncertainly. Then he grabbed the book and picked it up off the pedestal.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circular room was empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They walked back down the hallway. Empty. Into the three door room. The middle door still standing open. Just a barren alcove now. Empty. They stepped out onto the bridge. The fluorescent lights were off. The river had stopped running. No shapes swam in its currents. Empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Machiel stepped on the foot of the stairs, he looked back into the tomb. So lifeless now. Whatever dark magic had existed here before, he feared they now carried out with them.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was relieved to exit the archives and climb back onto his ship. He dropped the book on his console and sent his Troopers back to their posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, we’ve got an enemy ship inbound. leoliu86 of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Release the docking lines and detach from the archives. Shields at full power. Turn the ship 135 degrees to port. Nose up 30 degrees from plane. Thrusters full ahead. Meet them head-on.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that was quick.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the S.Q.U.I.D. leaders retiring, the rest of the warfleet had disbanded. Seeking refuge among the other alliances. Or starting their own anew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack granted shelter to as many ships as its starports could accomodate. Offering them hospitality and a new place to call home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were the displaced refugees of a fractured empire. In a galaxy torn apart by war.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leoliu86 either refused to accept the disbandment of his fleet. (An alliance he had dedicated his life towards serving.) Was stuck in a pre-programmed automated defense routine. Or was himself looting the coffers of the fallen empire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, he now engaged Machiel in battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ready the weapons for fire. Roborob, prepare boarding parties to target the enemy reactors. Fighter pilots, take out the enemy ACLs. Full power to lasers and missiles.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel opened The Book Of Secrets, “Let’s see what you have for me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A green heatless fire rose up from the pages. Swelling up Machiel’s arms and into the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Power surges started to sound alarms in the laser systems. Arcs of electricity and sparks began popping from the weapons casements. Rippling with a new unknown power they couldn’t quite contain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Open fire! Release that energy build-up before those lasers blow!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His lasers hammered into leoliu86 with enough force to rock the ship. Green fire crackling around the edge of the beams. Punching clear holes in the enemy shields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel’s fighters responded immediately and peppered the ship with more gunfire to widen the breaches.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strangely, Machiel’s missle bay 1 started firing EMPs at the enemy reactors. A target that would have zero impact against the enemy ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Missile Bay 1, retarget your EMPs on the enemy lasers. We are not clay pigeon shooting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Static. Nothing came back over the comms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Missile Bay 1, report.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Static. Still nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Trooper, head to Missle Bay 1 and report back to me with their status.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle was over in little more than a minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leoliu86’s shields were not built to withstand the massive amounts of energy surging from Machiel’s lasers. Once the reactors were distintegrated, his ship became nothing more than a powerless metal bucket floating through space.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, sir? I think you better get down here,” it was Trooper calling from Missile Bay 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle was a momentous victory, but how Missle Bay 1 had behaved was undismissable. Those EMPs would cost him an arm-and-a-leg to replace. Had it been a stronger enemy, their mistargetting could have cost him the battle. Machiel was not pleased.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He walked into Missle Bay 1, “Report.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, sir. The missile controls would not respond to our commands. The comms went silent and we couldn’t open the doors. We lost control of the room. The missiles just began firing on their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, I hesitate to say this. It was like it had become…. possessed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Book Of Secrets. Machiel remembered the green fire pouring forth from its pages. Up his arms. Into the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What had he brought onboard with them? What had he exposed to his ship and crew?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist012_MachielPt2.png&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist012_MachielPt2&quot; title=&quot;Machiel defeats leoliu86&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/06/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/06/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt2.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;11 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Book Of Secrets, pt. 1&amp;#58; The Unmarked Tomb&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-242&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #242.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was known as The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had been searching for the text ever since he had learned of its existence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by a great general during the late chinese Spring And Autumn Period, the book was said to contain powerful magic. Dangerous spells that could turn fields into mud. Grass into fire. Metal into sludge. Materialize entire armies out of thin air. Swallow enemies whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only a hundred copies had been made. Written on the cut slats of bamboo, stripped from the shields and spears of defeated enemies. Penned in ink squeezed from the bladders of octopi, cuttlefish and squid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books were feared for their secrets. Feared for the powers they could summon. Feared for whatever untold terrors they could pull from another dimension and unleash upon the cosmos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emperor looked upon the twisted misshapen form of his general, the green fires leaking from his eyes, and recognized the books for what they were. Evil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He ordered his lieutenants to gather together all known copies. Throw them in a massive pile. Douse them in kerosene. And burned. All of them. Each and every last malignant manuscript. Burned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All but one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One copy survived. Written in the general’s own hand. Bound together by hair from the emperor’s concubines, who he had executed for failing to carry out his orders. Hidden away in an unmarked tomb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the last copy. The Book Of Secrets. Waiting to be unearthed. Thousands upon thousands of years later. Waiting. Just Waiting. Until one day its secrets would be revealed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book was cursed.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel scoffed. He did not believe in old wives’ tales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had not achieved the rank of Wolf Lord because he cringed from danger. Nor would he have acquired the badges he so proudly wore now on his shoulder. Architect. Dreadnought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was a brilliant tactician. He had rightfully earned his place among the senior officers of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He understood the value of knowledge. Of strategy. He pursued any resource that might give him a fighting edge over his enemies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Book Of Secrets was written by a masterful general. The book would contain tactics he had used during battle to successfully overcome his enemies. That was all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Machiel discovered of the book’s existence, and then of its location, it became only a matter of timing. Of finding that right moment when he could steal in and claim his prize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book was buried in a tomb, deep in the archives of the S.Q.U.I.D. empire. He knew where. It became only a question of when.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the end of an era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaders of the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet announced their resignation. After the collapse of Sushi Train, the sudden peace that followed was unsettling. It allowed for reflection. A time for thought. A hard look upon themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how noble their intent for ruling the galaxy, no matter how great their magnanimity, they couldn’t escape the truth before them. It was because of their long rule, because of the enmity it had stirred, that had caused a Sushi Train to be born.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a truth, once recognized, they could not continue to bear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so, one by one, the leaders of the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet announced the end of their reign. One by one, they slowly filed out and flew their ships from the capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a long procession. All of the alliances were present. Dark Matter Heroes. Victrix Mortalis. Elder Drivers. Clan Zaki. Pillaging Scourge. A multitude of minor alliances. And Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A band started playing on one of the ships and scattered cheers began to erupt, but WarWolff growled at them. Commanding silence. This was not a celebration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a time for respect. A recognition of the strong leaders before them. An acknowledgment of the profound ways in which they had shaped the galaxy. Of the wars they had fought. The enemies they had withstood. The heavy burdens they had borne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a respect that could only be acknowledged by silence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silent nods. Silent salutes. Powerfully grave. The S.Q.U.I.D. leaders passed by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zulras&lt;br /&gt;
Stormhunter&lt;br /&gt;
CORSAIR&lt;br /&gt;
Myla&lt;br /&gt;
BeefFizelRoll&lt;br /&gt;
PuddingTown&lt;br /&gt;
Overhauled&lt;br /&gt;
Nightlane&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one, they flew their mighty warships to Lost Eden. Never to return. Never to fly again. Never to fight as one. A respected enemy. A shared ally. A proud fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the end of an empire. It was the end of an era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet was no more.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With so many on attendance at the procession, Machiel slipped into the capital unnoticed. Intent on pursuing his search for The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He docked outside the S.Q.U.I.D. archives. The building was fronted by massive white pillars and flowing silk banners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Huge oxygenators pumped out exorbitant amounts of ozone in front of the building, to create a small open atmosphere that quickly bled out into space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a breathable patio quite literally on the edge of space. It was the kind of waste and opulence that only the wealthy would indulge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel disembarked from the ship with two of his trusty Troopers by his side and entered the archives.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interior was enormous. Towering white colonnades stretched from floor to ceiling, with pillars as thick as old growth wood. While beautiful rounded domes of glass arched overhead, providing a full observatory onto the stars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel ignored the sights while his Troopers looked up in awe. Time was of the essence and he could not afford distraction. He led them into a small recessed alcove in the anterior of the building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressing a tile on the wall, he revealed a secret doorway. It opened onto a staircase that twisted downward into darkness. The foul stench of stagnant water rose up to greet them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clapping his hand over his mouth, Machiel stepped inside.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom of the stairway opened onto a wide cavern. Fluorescent lights, old and oddly placed, littered the sides of the stalactites and walls. Flickering on and off like torches under a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wooden bridge stretched before them over a river. As they crossed, they could see strange phantasmal shapes floating through the water underneath. Phosphorescent. Ghostly. Ethereal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curious, one of the Troopers reached an arm over the rail. Almost casual in response, one of the shapes floated closer to the surface. Mesmerizing. Iridescent like gasoline on water. Eager. Longing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Trooper reached out his hand to touch the surface…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel grabbed his wrist and looked at him sternly, “Do not touch the water.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Trooper gulped and pulled his hand back to his chest, rubbing his wrist. Looking over the rail, he watched as the ethereal shape floated away. Nonchalant. All things would come with time.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After crossing the bridge, they entered a broad chamber with three doors. The Room Of Probability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had been forewarned of this room when he learned of the book’s location. He would be given two guesses to determine the correct door. On his first guess, one of the other two doors would open to be revealed as the incorrect door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it became a question of which of the remaining two doors he would select for his second and final guess. Stick with his original choice? Or choose the other door?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had prepared in advance by studying the writings of an old probability wizard by the name of Vos Savant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the start of the test, all of the doors would share an equal probability of 1/3 chance of being correct. But according to Vos Savant, after the first guess and one of the doors had been eliminated, then the other door would now have a 2/3 chance of being the correct door. Whereas the original selection would only retain its 1/3 probability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it was always in your best odds to switch your guess to the other door.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel looked at his Trooper. He had grabbed his right hand. So he hazarded a guess that the right door was not the one that he wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for his first guess, using a dial on the floor, he selected the right door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response, the middle door opened to reveal a black hole. With shadowy tendrils fingering at the opening. Hungry to draw any into its arms. Into oblivion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only two doors remained to choose from. Right. His first pick. Or the other door. Left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following Vos Savant’s probability logic, Machiel chose the other and now turned the dial to the left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The left door opened onto a passageway.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They followed the passage down a long hall that opened on a circular room. The room was made of solid concrete. Cold and empty. Except for a stone pedestal that stood in the center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From a hole in the ceiling, rich light poured down from a blue star on top of the pedestal. Revealing a book. Bathed in pure, glittering starlight and opened to a single entry:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Know thyself, know thy enemies.&lt;br /&gt;
A thousand battles, a thousand victories.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally! The unmarked tomb. The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had found it at last.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/05/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/05/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt1.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;10 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Great White&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-240&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #240.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no atmosphere in space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Objects in light are painfully brighter. Blinding. Objects in shadow become black. A black without variation. Indistinguishable from anything else. Obscure. Invisible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without advanced augmented vision, it is difficult to see in space.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It swam at 200 meters under the sea. Just beyond the field of vision. Where there is little light. Where you were unsure whether you might have seen something? Or was your mind playing tricks with the darkness?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Captain _sharky_ flew a class 10 squid. The top of the hull was painted a murky green-grey. Along its underbelly, a pale ghostly white. A vicious red grin of white teeth blazened dangerously across the bow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The smile of Death. A great white shark. _sharky_’s smile.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It could smell blood in one part per million of seawater. It preyed on the wounded. The weak. The bleeding. The smell triggered a deep primal urge that focused every fiber of its body into one single response: Pursue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ was specialized in data collection and information processing. It had earned him the rank of Blood Knight among Wolfpack. He could extract minute bits of detail and translate them back into meaningful intel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had equipped his ship with a special pair of highly sensitive ducts in the forward bow. They could pick up small particles floating through space and determine their trajectory, speed and alien matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When two objects meet, they leave behind a residue of each other on the other’s surface. It is the nature of friction. It was this residue that _sharky_ was sifting for. Manufactured metal. Singed laser fire. Propulsion fuel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He called them “sniffers”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a ship struck these particles, it sent them flying off in opposite directions like a pool ball. All he had to do was trace the line back to its source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was how _sharky_ discovered his enemy. Floating along in deep space. Presuming his ship remained undetected. Ruby-Roo of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would discover his presumption was wrong.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ had equipped the front of his ship with a steel battering ram. Strong armor plates overlapping and stacked on top of each other. Reinforcing the entire forward bulkhead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missiles and laser fire worked great for surgical strikes. But _sharky_’s ship was a 45,000 ton juggernaut. The speed at which he pushed the engines was enough to melt the reactors. Nothing could withstand the force of impact he was about to unleash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He smashed into the hull of Ruby-Roo like a great white hitting a seal and breaking the surface of the water. Powerful jaws clamping down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby-Roo’s ship bent in half around _sharky_’s hull, hurtling them together madly at a new trajectory. Entangled. Ruptured steel tearing into each other. Locked in battle.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ had the initiative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His Interceptors flew out of the hangar like hornets from a kicked hive. Opening fire on the exterior of Ruby-Roo’s ship moments after impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teleporters were unnecessary. With the close proximity and devastation wrecked by the collision, boarders could simply walk onto the other ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following pre-determined attack plans, _sharky_ sent a Slimer to destroy the enemy turrets and ACLs. Following him, Lollita took out the enemy plasma cannons and engines. While his ship’s missiles peppered the enemy’s torpedo rooms. Leaving his lasers to work the medbay and finish off any wounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He hit at everything.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jarred. Ship schematics now obsolete. Weapons sluggish to respond. It was all Ruby-Roo could do to mount a counter-offensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He noticed a weak spot in _sharky_’s defenses. One of the reactors had been exposed by the breach of impact. Not to mention, the heavy strain _sharky_ had already put on them by red-lining the engines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All weapons target the enemy central reactor!”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ had grafted a wireless network of electroreceptors into his spine and fused them with steel. They could reach out to both his outer hull and internal systems, as well as extend beyond to any nearby relays that were broadcasting commands. Measuring the electromagnetic currents and various audio frequencies that were communicating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a very literal sense, he could “feel” space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_’s near-omniscient sensory equipment did not fail him. He heard Ruby-Roo’s order and responded immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The enemy is targeting our central reactor. Golden Boy, you’re with me. We are to keep that reactor online at all costs and keep our weapons firing. Should we fall, Invader, Verunus and Good student, you are to assume our places and protect that reactor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, you’re the captain of the ship! You can’t rush into enemy fire.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You heard me. Trooper, you have command while I am away. Gentlemen, you have your orders.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ was one of those rare leaders who would not ask of his crew anything that he would not demand of himself first. First to charge. First into battle. First to fall.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a lucky shot. A laser blast took him through the side as he was refastening a blown thermal coil and tightening the seal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laser fire from a ship’s weapons are not small. It punched a hole through half of _sharky_’s torso. It was fatal. He only had time enough to turn and see Golden Boy severed in half by the same laser beam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything went black. _sharky_ smiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black. It reminded him of space.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, can you hear me? Sir?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ was surprised to wake up. If what he was doing could be called waking up. It was certainly a consciousness, but unlike anything he had experienced before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, those electroreceptors you embedded in your spine acted as two-way relays. We were able to use the data they collected to artificially reconstruct your consciousness in the bridge’s central computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Our work is a little primitive by your standards, but with your expertise we thought you could improve on it once we brought you online.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah, that explained it. He felt so much bigger now. The entire ship. A bit stiff, but he could make upgrades. He would need to close those security holes in his relays. The same holes that had allowed his crew to restore his consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ruby-Roo? The battle? Golden Boy??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, we’re reading your thought output on the monitor. The battle was a victory. Your orders carried the day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Invader, Verunus and Good student rushed to the reactor room when they saw you fall. Your attack plan took apart Ruby-Roo’s ship piece-by-piece. It sort of just sloughed off our nose when the battle was through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But Golden Boy… We could not save him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was a good crewman. _sharky_ would remember his sacrifice.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new host body would be needed to represent himself among Wolfpack. A steel automaton should work. It would seem detached. The black eyes unreadable. The wolf cloak awkward on its shoulders. But considering what he had just been through, he was sure they would understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ was no longer captain of the ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ was the ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Great White.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/02/history-of-the-pack-the-great-white.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/02/history-of-the-pack-the-great-white.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;9 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Sushi Wars, pt. 4&amp;#58; Homecoming&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-239&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #239.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Wars were over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intergalactic struggle for supremacy had ended. Every alliance felt the deep tears in loyalty that the war had cost them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New friendships were made. New enemies were sworn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone was touched by it. It was like new skin regrowing after a cut. Sensitive. Stinging. Scarred.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet reclaimed dominance over the galaxy. With a recognition, and now deeper distrust, of the rampant opportunism prevalent among the mercenary ships of its fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Victrix Mortalis were the most effected. They had decimated their ranks to lead The Sushi Train initiative. It would take weeks for them to refill their numbers. And longer still to recover from the bitter defeat. A victory that should have been their’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lone unknown saboteur had decimated Sushi Train with a single attack. There would be a price on his head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suspiciously, the Elder Drivers were the only alliance to come out ahead from the struggle. Pushing out Dark Matter Heroes and closely contending with S.Q.U.I.D. now for power.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack was not untouched by the Sushi Wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone was returning home. Those who had joined in the struggle, a little less sure of themselves than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would take powerful overtures and good-natured ribaldry to overcome any underlying resentment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, this was our greatest strength in Wolfpack. We were fiercely loyal to each other. A quality that transcended any other alliance. We were wolves.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel, Test girl, fritz, SCVsUnion and myself were the first to return. Omega was the closest to Wolfpack, so our trip was the shortest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was not uncommon to send officers and flagships to omega pack to help watch over the young pups. Given the instability of the galaxy and hostility of the Sushi Wars, we had simply sent a few more ships than usual to protect our growing kin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, the welcomes were brief. A few hugs. A couple pats on the pack. It didn’t matter, it sure felt good to be home.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx was the next to return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could see the heavy weight on his shoulders. His loneliness among S.Q.U.I.D. The wounds he had suffered at the constant battery of Sushi Train warships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It did not matter that his allies had won. Without his pack, the victory was empty. Meaningless. His scars ran deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff was wise. He had assembled the officers in full ceremony to receive him. WarWolff, Machiel, Seq, Hyten and I were all present. Heavy fur cloaks. Dark glittering eyes. Menacing. Dangerous. Bonded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx needed to see us for what we were. Wolves. He needed to see through us what he was. A wolf. We lent him our strength to draw from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was with his pack again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His pack was with him.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff squeezed xEEVEEx’s shoulder and gave him a long stare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a look of knowing. You could see the deep lines around WarWolff’s eyes. The heavy creases in his brow. The painful sacrifices that he too had made for the pack. They were scars they now both shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Welcome home, xEEVEEx.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stepped forward next, “You’ll be needing this back.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grabbed the edges of xEEVEEx’s cloak and pulled them together across his chest, fastening them in place with the pendant of the wolf mouth made of silver. Signifying his resumed leadership over omega pack. I was not gentle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“May it keep your fur cloak around your shoulders.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx smiled at me and patted me on the arm.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hyten stepped forward, holding forth (at arm’s length) a squirming, slashing, growling, fluffy, little monster. It was a tiliger cub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I looked over your terror while you were away, xEEVEEx. I had a fish tank. It ate them all. I think you would be proud.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx grabbed the cub, hugging it in his arms and ruffling up the mane on top of its head, as it swat and snapped playfully at his fingers. Hyten looked on with distaste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx stepped alongside WarWolff, resuming his position among Wolfpack. Awaiting our next officers.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara and Deathlord291 were the last to arrive. Looking disoriented and confused. The sabotage and resulting disbandment of Sushi Train took everyone by surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was good that our pack held together so well during the Sushi Wars. It was what the two needed. Stability. A good strong rock to call home. Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We received them with laughter and gracious hugs.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 rubbed his backside, still smarting from a kick, “Dang xEEVEEx! You have one vicious bite. You really caught me with my pants down out there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What do you expect? You were in Sushi Train. You should have picked a better toilet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 barked a laugh.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned from the Sushi Wars. We learned about ourselves. Our loyalties not only to the pack, but towards each other. Wolfpack was stronger for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was good to have us all back together again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/01/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-homecoming.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/01/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-homecoming.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;8 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Sushi Wars, pt. 3&amp;#58; The Merciless&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-238&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #238.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Train was swelling to massive proportions. Bigger and bigger ships were joining the new armada every day. Everyone had a bone to pick with the long oppresive rule of the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Train had greater numbers. More powerful warships. Greater communication arrays. Drawing more recruits into battle. Bulstering their lines with stronger attack formations. Tightening their ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Elder Drivers betrayal, they had effectively divided the S.Q.U.I.D. forces by a third. Sushi Train had routed the remaining S.Q.U.I.D ships back to their empire’s capital, where they now sat entrenched. Their guns bristling to defend their home starport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A massive armada of Sushi Train surrounded the capital like the metal rings of a bear-trap. Sharp spikes pointing inwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There would be a final confrontation. There would be one last engagement between Sushi Train and S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet. For supremacy. For freedom. For the fate of all the galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There would be an end.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 had joined with Sushi Train to fight in the final struggle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His ship was a class 10 pirate. Black against the black of space. A skull-and-crossbones painted brazenly in ghostly white across its hull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would have been undetected. His ship blended well with the black sky, save when he crossed over a planet or star. But Deathlord291’s strategy was not of surprise. Deathlord291 wanted to be feared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His enemies could hear him coming from a light sector away. He had mounted powerful speakers on the outside of his ship. Cranking out over 10,000 watts of sound. As he flew into battle, he turned up the volume dial to full blast. Playing the song “Du hast” from an old metal relic band of the 20th century known as Rammstein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no atmosphere in space to dampen the flow of sound. Any ship without built-in audio suppression, would have suffered the force at full impact. Exploding internal systems and seizing the crew with immediate cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His enemies could hear him coming. But because of his dark camoflauge against space, they could not see where.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Wars were prime feeding ground. There were so many ships filling the sky, you could barely see the stars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 fought like a rock skipping across water. Targeting smaller squid ships and punching a hole through their structure before they could turn to meet the assualt. Leaving each enemy ship to slowly turn upwards in space with internal systems combusting, as he moved on to destroy the next target.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 was Merciless.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One enemy squid flew out to meet the challenge. Cpt. Yami of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291’s weapons were set to automatically target the missile room of an enemy ship. And to keep firing at that target until they punched a hole clean through to the other side of space. They bored him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He switched on the monitor next to his console and picked up a joystick. He had recalibrated the feed from his ship’s internal security cameras to display as an old arcade game: Pac-Man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had recoded the game and reversed its mechanics. Enemy boarders were the munching round pizza-faced avatars called Pac-Men. His own defending crew were the deadly one-shot ghosts. Blinky. Pinky. Inky. And Clyde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 huddled over his joystick. Cackling maniacly, “Who’s coming to play?”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cpt. Yami targeted the lasers on Deathlord291’s ship. Taking down one laser at a time and then moving onto the next. The first boarder he would send was a First Sergeant Xin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the only boarder he would send.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deathlord291 wore the arm of an old plastic doll around his neck. It was a string of twine wrapped around the doll’s wrist that sort of just hung across his chest. You could see the plastic plug of where the arm would attach to a doll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know that Deathlord291 even knew that he wore it. Let alone ask him why. He was certifiably insane. He had the drip-feed of a coffee pot plugged into his arm. A juiced-up caffeine junky. It should have killed him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His crew were walking animatronics that he had assembled himself out of metal parts and soldered electronics. He put buckets on their necks for heads and painted them with cheery smiling faces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were slow and awkward. With jittering movements and popping gears. But they were made of steel. They were tough. They could withstand a fair amount of abuse from enemy boarders before returning fire.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xin had no idea what he was jumping into. The lights were off when he boarded Deathlord291’s reactor. He could only see by a flashlight, that he had thankfully strapped to the muzzle of his gun before teleporting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But he could hear them coming. Clanking feet and scraping metal. He detonated the reactor as quickly as he could, before running to the next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inky met him there. His bright, painted, cheery face under flashlight was an absolute horror in darkness. It was a brutal exchange of gunfire before Xin could dispatch the robot. By the time he had, Blinky, Pinky and Clyde had arrived to reinforce their fallen friend. Smiling cheerfully. Xin didn’t stand a chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back on Cpt. Yami’s ship, all they heard over Xin’s comm was the sound of gunfire, screams, and the hollow eerie boxed soundbits of an old retro arcade game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one else boarded Deathlord291’s ship.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing that Cpt. Yami would send no other boarders, Deathlord291 grew tired of the battle. He flipped his monitor to an old cartoon show: Invader Zim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cpt. Yami’s ship was destroyed by his weapons without further acknowledgement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Immersed as he was, Deathlord291 did not notice the dark shadow that passed over his ship’s stern. Heavily coasting toward the heart of Sushi Train command.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fleets were linked together by powerful communication arrays mounted on each ship. The arrays acted largely as receivers, but they could communicate with their fellow ships at a limited range. The command ships though, were equipped with powerful relays that could broadcast commands across the entire fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The saboteur that struck at the central command of Sushi Train was unlike anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A ship painted with The Sushi Train’s emblem, and boasting their own powerful communication damper, rammed into the fleet’s central command. Immediately silencing all broadcasts across the fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Sushi Train commanders boarded the traitorous vessel to demand answers, there was no one on board. The ship was a spook. Deserted. Empty. It was a ghost ship.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Train fleet, made up of ships like Deathlord291 and Sumara, were engaged in their own separate battles. When each engagement was finished, they would receive their following orders for attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when central command was knocked out, there were no further orders coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They would wait. And wait. And wait. Until finally, uncertain of what else to do. They simply flew home to their former alliances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no final confrontation. No last stand. No epic glorious battle. No terms of surrender. No victory or defeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a war concluded in silence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With The Sushi Train disbanded, the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet quietly resumed their place of authority over the galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist008_SushiWarsPt3_Deathlord291_SushiTrain.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist008_SushiWarsPt3_Deathlord291_SushiTrain&quot; title=&quot;Deathlord291 defeats Cpt. Yami&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/31/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-the-merciless.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/31/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-the-merciless.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;7 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Sushi Wars, pt. 2&amp;#58; The Proposal&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-236&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #236.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx was the first among Wolfpack to join in the altercations between the S.Q.U.I.D. Warfleet and Sushi Train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It began as wars often do. With excitement. Hunger for glory. A chance to prove your mettle in battle. About picking a side and fighting alongside your new brothers in arms. That the war would be over quickly. Your side stand victorious. And count yourself a proud hero among those who had fought. Bloodied. Glorious. Triumphant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wars do not go that way.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moment xEEVEEx stepped from Wolfpack, it closed its ranks behind him. In Wolfpack he was a senior officer. Commanding a position of Lt. Colonel, second only to WarWolff. Now he flew alongside the behemoth titans of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet. He was small. He was rank-and-file. He was cannon fodder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sushi Train was especially gunning for any new recruits the S.Q.U.I.D. may draft into its ranks. They would not allow the S.Q.U.I.D. to bulster their defenses and refill the gaping holes the Elder Drivers had left behind with their betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx was a small rock attempting to fill a missing brick in a stone wall. Sushi Train hammered him relentlessly. Without his pack behind him, it was all he could do to fend them off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brothers in arms who had first joined with xEEVEEx, to answer the summons of their S.Q.U.I.D. allies, were now absent. Deserted. Defected. Or destroyed. He sat alone at a table unto himself. Without his pack. A pawn in a much bigger game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the table before him, xEEVEEx rested his hand on his old fur cloak.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meeting of the pack leaders for the future of Wolfpack was still underway. WarWolff stepped into his ring of officers. Commanding their attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was I who proposed the super-alliance to dismantle S.Q.U.I.D.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any enmity between xEEVEEx and myself dissolved immediately. What? WarWolff? The idea for an alliance among the other fleets had came from our commander?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I met with leaders of the other fleets and proposed that we band together our best ships to surmount the S.Q.U.I.D. war machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The galaxy has grown stagnant under S.Q.U.I.D. rule. Their high tariffs and heavy taxes are strangling all of our fleets. Wolfpack among them. While S.Q.U.I.D. warships grow stronger by the wealth and continue to solidify their power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Victrix Mortalis took leadership of the initiative and carried it out. It was a pact that leaders of all the fleets agreed to. Clan Zaki. Pillaging Scourge. Elder Drivers. Dark Matter Heroes. And Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The S.Q.U.I.D. must come down.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx and I looked at each other in disbelief. WarWolff continued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have spoken with Sumara. She has agreed to join the Sushi Train as representative of Wolfpack and uphold our pledge with the other fleets. Just as xEEVEEx serves as a representative of us to our allies among S.Q.U.I.D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Any who seek glory and wish to join in the war between S.Q.U.I.D. or Sushi Train have my approval to do so. You will be stronger for it. I will remain in Wolfpack as leader and provide stability for our pack through these difficult times. We will not commit our full forces to either side in this confrontation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wolfpack will stand apart. We will reserve our ships. We will remain strong while the rest of the galaxy tears itself to pieces.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DeathLord291 stepped forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will join the Sushi Train with Sumara. The S.Q.U.I.D. have lorded their dominance over us for too long. I hunger for calamari.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t believe what I was hearing. I looked at them each in turn. DeathLord291? Sumara? WarWolff? These were our officers. Wolfpack! How could they join with another alliance? ANY alliance?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was disgusted. I turned on my heel to walk away.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel placed a hand against my chest to stop me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, I will join with you brother to look over our omega packmates. Our hearts are in the pack. Test girl, fritz and SCVsUnion will join with us as well. They are strong ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You and I know the leviathons that are out there. The hulking steel monstrosities floating through deep space. You and I have both faced them. We know the dangers. You know our omega pack stands no chance without our support.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bowed my head. There were no words against wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are not alone in the galaxy. There are too many alliances for Wolfpack to face them all. WarWolff must gamble with the other fleet leaders to serve in the best interests of our pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You and I are not diplomats. Our hearts are only in the pack. xEEVEEx and Sumara are our best foreign diplomats. Seq and Hyten are our native representatives here at home. DeathLord291 is just a killing machine.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both DeathLord291 and I snorted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Trust in your pack, ArchNadeom.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah Arch,” smirked Sumara. “Think we’d leave for good and let you have all the puppy snacks?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all laughed.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx stepped forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, you are the most loyal wolf I know.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx unclasped the silver pendant from his cloak. It was of an open wolf’s mouth made of silver. It represented his position as leader of omega pack. WarWolff wore one as well made of gold. xEEVEEx fastened the silver pendant to my cloak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Look after omega until I return.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could see in his eyes the battles he had been through. The storms he had weathered. I had always had the pack with me. xEEVEEx was out there alone. The S.Q.U.I.D. cloak he wore. Upholding former alliances. He was a target for everybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked at him again with new respect. He was a tough dog. He may wear a squid cloak now, but he has the heart of a wolf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reached out a hand to clasp his.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Until you return, brother.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel placed his hand on our’s. Then Sumara. Then DeathLord291. Then Hyten, Seq, and finally WarWolff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff took up the pack’s call. His officers answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“For the Wolfpack.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“a-Woooooooo!!!”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/29/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-the-proposal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/29/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-the-proposal.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;6 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Sushi Wars, pt. 1&amp;#58; A Break In Ranks&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-235&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #235.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It smelled of rotten fish. Every great alliance was involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victrix Mortalis&lt;br /&gt;
Clan Zaki&lt;br /&gt;
Pillaging Scourge&lt;br /&gt;
Elder Drivers&lt;br /&gt;
Dark Matter Heroes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The top ace captains had broken their former allegiances and formed together a new alliance, The Sushi Train. Its sole purpose: To topple the mighty S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was ugly business. Dirty tactics were employed on all sides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top brass of Victrix Mortalis were leading the strike. Promising high payouts for any ace ship willing to join the Sushi Train. High-ranking captains from both Clan Zaki and Pillaging Scourge quickly took up the summons, crippling and leaving their own alliances defenseless. It was within days that Dark Matter Heroes joined as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Elder Drivers had joined with S.Q.U.I.D. only the week before. The S.Q.U.I.D., in honor of the new allegiance, had culled their numbers. Making room for the more powerful Elder Driver ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But after only a few days, the Elder Drivers betrayed them and broke ranks. Joining with Sushi Train instead. Leaving S.Q.U.I.D. that much weaker than before. Now with huge gaps in their defenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The S.Q.U.I.D. were desperate and losing control of the galaxy. It reached out to its former alliances with pleas to refill its missing ranks and fight off the growing threat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were one of those former alliances. Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all dirty.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack officers met in council to determine the future of the pack. It was a grove on Omega, circled by trees, with the moon shining in full through the canopy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff, Machiel, DeathLord291, Sumara, Hyten, Seq, and I, ArchNadeom, were all present. Exchanging stories of triumphant victories and beaten adversaries, while we waited for our remaining officers to arrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx stepped into the grove. I growled under my breath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx had cast off his fur cloak, and in its place, was now wearing one of the silk pearlescent mantles belonging to the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hello squid,” smirked Sumara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx smiled at his old friend. 
“The battle for galactic supremacy goes poorly for our allies. The threat of the Sushi Train continues to advance. We joined together before with S.Q.U.I.D. to bring down the Old Drivers. And they have always had our back. They are our friends. Our allies. They call on us now to join their numbers and help fight off this new enemy. I have accepted the call. So long as the war endures, I will stand alongside them and defend our allies, the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are wolves. Not squid,” I growled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, the S.Q.U.I.D. have promoted prosperity throughout the galaxy. Yes at times heavy-handed, but that is to be expected when maintaining an empire. If we do not join with them, then our pack, our lives, our prestige as captains, so far as we know them, may perish. The empire may fall.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let it. We are wolves.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We growled at each other. xEEVEEx and I locked stares. Black eyes burrowing into each other’s skull. It was a battle of wills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was not a proud moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the other officers were wise. Standing aloof. Keeping their silence.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara Of The Stout Heart stepped between us and broke the tension. Placing a hand on both our arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The arguments have been made. Your counsels have been heard. WarWolff is our leader. Only he can decide the future of the pack.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx and I stepped back and resumed our places among the circle. Still glowering at each other under our brows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We awaited the command of our leader. WarWolff.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where would we stand in the dark days ahead? Would our packmates remain true? What was the future of Wolfpack?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/28/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-a-break-in-ranks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/28/history-of-the-pack-the-sushi-wars-a-break-in-ranks.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;5 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Gauntlet&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-234&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #234.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It spoke of redemption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion looked down at his hand.  Or at least, what had once been his hand.  Now it was a metal attachment. A steel prosthetic. A fist of clanking digits and whirling gyros. A robotic imitation of his missing limb. A reminder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was still getting used to the neural implants that corded their way up his arm and into his brain. It was a hand that did not feel like a hand. Like he had stuck his arm in a garbage disposal and the metal thing that had clamped down had suddenly become his hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Between the pain, the phantom sensations of the missing limb, and the unintuitive way in which the robotics responded, it felt alien. Foreign. Unnatural. It was a reminder.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weeks before they had spotted a foreign ship moving along the edge of one of their borders. SCVsUnion was on patrol. He had clear orders from Lt. Colonel xEEVEEx to engage any ship that trespassed on Wolfpack territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, we have identified the ship. It’s a class 9 pirate. Hypnosia of Elder Drivers.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion snorted. Elder Drivers? One of the newer alliances. Slowly growing in power. Carving off larger and larger pieces of the galaxy, and growing more and more hungry every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Couple of upstarts getting pretty full of themselves. Now they dared to cut into Wolfpack territory?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They’re a nobody. Destroy them. Follow standard attack procedures. I’ll be in my quarters. Find me when the battle is finished.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the moment SCVsUnion stepped off the bridge, everything went wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The enemy Hypnosia had dropped a Rocky boarder on their ship, that was tearing up their reactors like he was digging for a bone. And while the crew scrambled to repair the damage he unleashed, Hypnosia’s guns drilled a hole through their turret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make matters worse, the ship’s targetting system was on the fritz. And kept bouncing between well-armored systems, rather than exploiting a punctured hole in the enemy’s defense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all SCVsUnion could do to get back to the bridge and jump in an escape pod. He reached a hand through the door to press the ship’s emergency escape. But as the hull buckled, the automated systems kicked in and the door snapped shut. The crew, the cargo, and his hand, all went down with the ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hulk. Collins. Monk. Da Qiao. Abu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All good crewmen. All lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion looked down at the metal thing attached to his arm. The Gauntlet. It was a defeat he would not forget.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Elder Drivers were a build-up of a former alliance. The powerful P.R.C. Fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their newness was deceiving. The Elder Drivers were seasoned ships with plenty of battles under their belt from their former days with P.R.C. Fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the P.R.C. Fleet fell apart, having suffered heavy losses under incursions from the other alliances, many of its flagships and key officers banded together for survival to form a new alliance. The Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slowly closing their ranks, they were reclaiming what had once belonged to the mighty P.R.C. Fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were scarred. They were bitter. They were not to be taken lightly.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took weeks for SCVsUnion to assemble a new crew, hardier than before, and get another ship ready for battle. This time a class 10 federation. One of the big rigs. He wasn’t messing around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as his ship pulled out of dry dock, an enemy ship was already there to greet him. Hypnosia of Elder Drivers. So we meet again. Must have gotten gutsy after his last victory. Opening fire the moment his ship pulled out.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion flexed the fingers of his gauntlet one by one, then closed them into a fist. He would not underestimate his enemy again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the enemy guns pounding on their shields, SCVsUnion stood from his captain’s chair and called an assembly. Then walked to the teleporter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He did not hurry. He knew his ship. His shields would hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had prepared a special tactic for just such an attack. He called it, “Defensive Boarding.” He knew his enemy well.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crew were anxious to be standing on ceremony while the ship was under attack. You could hear the barrage of enemy fire chewing away at the shields. The occassional ping as a shot got through to the hull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion stepped up to the crewman who would make the first boarding. Oliver, in his green power armor. Grabbing the shoulder of Oliver’s bandolier of gas grenades, he gave it a tug and straightened them across Oliver’s chest. Then gave him a nod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boarding an enemy ship was risky business. Suicidal. Boarding plans were prepared before battle. Before you knew the layout of the enemy ship or the arrangement of its crew. You could very well be jumping into a 3-gun salute of your own funeral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had picked up Oliver from one of the local taverns. Sitting in a corner, keeping to himself. Everyone giving him a wide berth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the quiet ones you were wisest to fear. They were the most unexpected. The most dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now standing before Oliver in the teleporter, ready to board the enemy ship, SCVsUnion spoke no words. Oliver would not hear them. He would accept no praise or commendation for himself ahead of his ship or his pack. His loyalty was fierce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Standing before him as captain, his presence acknowledging his courage, was the most Oliver would accept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion did not say the orders. Oliver knew what to do.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their assault on the enemy ship began the moment Oliver breached the enemy teleporter. He closed his facemask and switched on his suit’s internal recirculating air, dropping a grenade of poison gas in the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the enemy crew coughing and disoriented, Oliver quickly exited the room and barred the doors behind him with one of the ship’s fire axes. Trapping the enemy crew inside with the deadly gas. He then beelined straight for the enemy hanger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their second boarder to the enemy ship, a man the crew nicknamed “The Monkey King”, secured the shield room. Effectively destroying the enemy shields. He then headed for the teleporter, eliminating any enemy crew that still remained after the gases had dissipated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oliver was met in the hanger room by a third boarder in green power armor. Facemask closed with internal air recirculating, and dropped his own grenade of poison gas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the key rooms of the enemy ship secured, SCVsUnion leisurely dismantled the rest of the enemy with his ship’s weapons.  This was a victory he wanted to savor.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion was the last to board the enemy ship. The enemy crew had been dispatched and the ship was floating sideways at a weird angle, slowly tilting upwards. Blackened and stripped from the inside out. Little more than a husk of the powerful warship it had once been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion stepped onto the enemy bridge and placed his gauntlet on the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have redeemed you, my fallen crew. I cannot restore your lives. May I reclaim your honor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a sobering victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCVsUnion. The Gauntlet of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist005_SCVsUnion.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist005_SCVsUnion&quot; title=&quot;SCVsUnion defeats Hypnosia&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/27/history-of-the-pack-the-gauntlet.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/27/history-of-the-pack-the-gauntlet.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;4 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Of The Stout Heart&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-232&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #232.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a bold move against the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack had been targetting S.Q.U.I.D. ships for weeks with little gain. Even the lower ranks of S.Q.U.I.D. put up a vicious fight. For every victory claimed by Wolfpack, the S.Q.U.I.D. made them pay with heavy losses. And for each S.Q.U.I.D. defeated, they quickly filled their ranks with newer and yet more powerful ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the senior officers of Wolfpack, and of them only a few, WarWolff, xEEVEEx, and Machiel, dared to confront the S.Q.U.I.D. fighting elite. We were outgunned. Outnumbered. We were losing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the Stout of Heart took up courage. It was time for a new offensive. One that struck at the heart of the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara, senior officer of Wolfpack, was our secret weapon.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had been planning this attack for weeks, ever since the war began. Carefully selecting and upgrading her systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was to penetrate behind enemy lines and strike at their leader, the oppressive and mighty general of the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet, PuddingTown. By cutting off the head of their leadership, that the ranks of the S.Q.U.I.D. would crumble from within.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a dangerous assignment. The S.Q.U.I.D. flew in tight circling formations around their center, protecting their general with a wall of ships. Each ring of defense growing stronger and stronger, and weaving itself more tightly as she would push further in.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff placed a hand on Sumara’s shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was not easy selecting an officer for such a mission. There was just no other choice. The S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet was too powerful for a frontal assualt, as the last weeks of battle had painfully proven. It would require guile and courage to infiltrate the enemy lines. Sumara was their best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clasping Sumara’s shoulders, WarWolf looked her in the eye and then gave her a powerful hug. He may never see his friend again.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the mission, Sumara had selected one of the dorito-styled ships that was popular among the S.Q.U.I.D.  “Dorito.” She smirked at the name. Her ship would devour plenty of those in the days ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her captain’s chair was covered by a thick rug of the softest fur. By her side, she kept a flask filled with a thick dark liquid and some undefinable thing sloshing around within.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a rumor circulating among the ship. Her former firstmate, the Trumpsta, had made the mistake of staring at her chest instead of her eyes as she dictated orders. So she cut out his eyes and saved them as a souveneir in her flask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would she correct them? It kept them focused on their duties. And amused her greatly to see one of her crew go pale whenever she took a sip.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir! We’ve got something on the scanner.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara stood from her chair and approached the station, “Is it him?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Reading the output now, sir…. PuddingTown of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally. Weeks of preparation and crawling behind enemy lines had payed off. The head of the beast. It was a great leviathon of a ship. A federation class 10, fully stocked and bristling with guns and warheads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir! They’ve pierced our cover! Enemy ship is opening fire!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Shields and weapons to maximum power. Train all guns and missiles on the enemy shields. Slimer, head to the teleporter and prepare for boarding. Let’s see if we can pull the tentacles off their king.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, I’m reporting security breaches in Reactor Rooms 1 and 2.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara snorted. Enemy boarders? Is that the best you’ve got?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engineering Vehicles and Visiri Capn’s, report to the reactor rooms and get them back online. Slimer, board the enemy ship and cut power to their shields. All weapons retarget and train fire on the enemy fusion reactor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see how you like that. Two can play this game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, our teleporter is sustaining heavy enemy fire!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Crew, cease all boarding maneuvers. Engineering Vehicles and Visiri Cap’ns rush to the teleporter for emergency repairs. Time your repairs between enemy fire. We’ll cover you as best we can with the shields.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir! Our hull is collapsing! We can’t withstand that much firepower. Enemy guns are punching a hole clean through our ship!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All crew report to your gun posts! Keep those shells firing and the missile bays full. And keep targeting that reactor! It’s a race against death, boys. Make your pack proud. a-Wooooooooo!!!”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a battle of legends. Sumara destroyed the great PuddingTown of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet and cut the head off their empire. Wolfpack mounted a full offensive, taking advantage of the confusion and crippled leadership, and nipping at the heels of S.Q.U.I.D. warships as they beat a hasty retreat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff was proud to see his friend again. It was a victory worthy of celebration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara Of The Stout Heart. Hero of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist004_Sumara.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist004_Sumara&quot; title=&quot;Sumara defeats PuddingTown&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/25/history-of-the-pack-of-the-stout-heart.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/25/history-of-the-pack-of-the-stout-heart.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
