<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wolfpack Alliance</title>
    <description>Legendary Alliance in PixelStarships - a Mobile Sci-Fi MMO Game</description>
    <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wolfpackpss.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 13:15:31 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 13:15:31 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>History of the Pack &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;First Howl&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;stardate-231&quot;&gt;Stardate #231&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Enemy boarders have taken the first lower reactor. What are your orders, sir?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was supposed to be an easy target. They picked up the scan from the last starport. A fat merchant vessel heavy with minerals and gas. But that wasn’t what was waiting for them when they jumped into the sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the nebula, with full guns blazing to greet them, was a class 10 squid mercenary–S4G3 of Federation. It had been a setup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Enemy guns targetting the second forward reactor. Sir! What are your orders?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crew had responded admirably and jumped to their battle-stations. But it didn’t matter. The enemy ship had the drop on us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our captain, the Evil General, was the first to launch a boarding party against the enemy shield. But as soon as the teleporter opened, he was met with a smoking las-cannon. fritz looked down at the gaping hole in the General’s chest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The General had been a good tactician. Hard, but he had the men’s respect. Rest well, you old dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;fritz, sir! You are captain now! What are your orders?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was Thing 1 talking. The General had picked him and his brother up in a dive bar on one of the outer sectors, slugging it out fist-for-fist with the locals. They were a couple of cyborgs, with whirling gears, robotic arms and mechanized organs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem was, you couldn’t tell them apart. So the General had nicknamed them Thing 1 and Thing 2, after some old trashy nursery rhyme. There was a reason he was called Evil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The shields can’t hold! The second forward reactor is taking heavy damage!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our ship was only a class 6. Totally outmatched against the barrage of enemy firepower facing us. With S.Q.U.I.D. holding dominance over the galaxy and upgrading their fleet to the new class 10s, there were a lot of older squid models lying around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The galaxy was not a safe place. A simple conversation with another ship could quickly escalate into an exchange of fire. Massive gang alliances had cut up the sectors and prowled hungrily on ships stranded in space. You did not want to fly alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had joined with omega pack for a time. It was a younger sister alliance of Wolfpack. Young pups full of life. As yet, untested and unscarred by the cold brutality of space. But what they lacked in experience, they made up for with energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still think on them fondly. Always proud to meet an omega packmate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, battle-hardened and ready to test our mettle against the outer sectors, we moved up into Wolfpack. Sleek black ships. Dark heavy fur coats. Smoldering black eyes burning with a deeper fire. Grim. Dark. Menacing. Dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting a fellow Wolfpack is always a heavy affair. Filled with deep respect and powerful oaths of allegiance to the pack. They still give me the shivers. Glad they’re on our side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The second forward reactor is down. Third mid reactor is under heavy fire!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fritz looked up from the Evil General’s dead corpse. There was a change in him. You could see it. A set in the jaw. The squaring of the shoulders. The crew looked to him. He had assumed command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Thing 1, board the enemy ship and take down their reactor. Oliver, man the guns and concentrate all fire on their shields. Yusi, load the Penetrators and take out those missile rooms. Buy us some time to get our shields back online. Thing 2 protect that third reactor with your life. If we lose that last reactor our ship is dead!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the Wolfpack! a-Wooooooooo!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the first howl. It was a sound that would echo deep throughout Wolfpack. His packmates heard and took up the call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;a-Woooooooo!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/24/history-of-the-pack-first-howl.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/24/history-of-the-pack-first-howl.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>History of the Pack &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;A New Guard&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;stardate-230&quot;&gt;Stardate #230&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a time of change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Old Drivers alliance had been broken. It was a bloody war. It took the very best of Wolfpack and the very best of S.Q.U.I.D. to band together to overthrow the Old Drivers. You can still see their cracked ships and broken hulls. Scarring the horizon like tombstones of former days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a time for change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one, the old guard of the wolfpack, TurdSmoothie, Stodz, Amah, and others, put down their arms and walked into the distance. No songs were sung. There were no clasps of hand or looks backward. No words were spoken. It was not their way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was agreed that Caxy would remain. No longer flying beside his pack, but to counsel. To guide. To lend his heroic crew and voice of wisdom in the dark times ahead. His days for glory were past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a time for new leadership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new pack assembled on their home planet Omega. Their fur coats bristling and eyes burning black. Hungry for glory. Omega was a good place to assemble. It was where it all began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff stood before them. Tall against the horizon, a full moon casting him in white. Caxy slid off his old mantle, a heavy dark fur cloak cut from battle, and placed it on WarWolff’s shoulders. A hand on his shoulder. A hard look in the eye. No words were spoken. It was not their way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would he live up to the demands expected of him? Would he bring his pack glory? Would he lead them to triumph over their enemies? These are questions that only a great leader asks of himself. Only a great leader thinks of his pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff knew what was ahead. He could see it in his pack’s eyes. Knew what they expected of him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;xEEVEEx&lt;/strong&gt;  - &lt;em&gt;The Flint-Eyed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machiel&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;The Strong&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sumara&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;Of The Stout Heart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DeathLord291&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;The Merciless&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seq&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;Keeper Of The Way&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hyten&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;em&gt;The Sentinel&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All proud officers of the new pack. He would need their strength in the coming battles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the destruction of the Old Drivers, the S.Q.U.I.D. assumed dominance of the galaxy. The Victrix Mortalis soon became their lackeys, with the strange alien Dark Matter Heroes shadowing every of S.Q.U.I.D.’s moves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack was under a change and could not make such a bid. Clan Zaki, Pillaging Scourge and Wolfpack were left to scrap for whatever was left among a scrabble of lower alliances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Betrayal. It was not a word that sat lightly for WarWolff. He had joined with S.Q.U.I.D. to take down the Old Drivers. They were his former allies. His friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Betrayal. He could see it in his officers’ eyes. Too long had they lived under S.Q.U.I.D. rule. Too long had they lived under the shadow of its powerful overreaching arm. He knew what they expected of him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff turned to the full moon and raised his fist in the air, &lt;em&gt;“For the Wolfpack!!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/23/history-of-the-pack-a-new-guard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/23/history-of-the-pack-a-new-guard.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>History of the Pack &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;First Days&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;stardate-229&quot;&gt;Stardate #229&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;em&gt;ArchNadeom&lt;/em&gt;, Keeper Of Records, write of the first days of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The galaxy was different in those times. Before it was carved up between the alliances. Before the patriarchs sat heavy on the stars like Titans overshadowing the fates. It was a time of Newness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could smell the openness of the galaxy. The freedom of undivided space. Feel the eagerness for the first tournament. See the solar rise over a planet’s edge and bathe the galaxy in gold. It was a new dawn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was in those times that &lt;em&gt;Caxy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;TurdSmoothie&lt;/em&gt;, two friends, two warriors, two wolves, struck their hands together in brotherhood and Wolfpack was born. Know their names and remember.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caxy of the gold-plated guns, light reflecting off his ship bright like a new star. TurdSmoothie alongside all guns blazing like a mad dog. With their pack behind them. Stodz The First, first victor of the first tournament, single-handededly pounding through wave after wave of enemy ship to claim first trophy and forever a legend. Amah The Tall who stood proudly among his brothers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was before our voices. Before the howl. When our great WarWolff was himself a young pup. And silent as a fleet they flew dark and deadly into battle. Know their names and remember.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quiet they rest now. No longer does Caxy’s gold plates catch the sun. No longer do our enemies fear TurdSmoothie’s name. Feel the scar across Amah’s hull. What battles have you fought, old wolf? Rest your head on Stodz console. What secrets do you hide? No longer do they run with us among the stars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel their power. Take their strength. They are your ancestors. Know what it means to be a wolf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;a-Woooooooo!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/22/history-of-the-pack-first-days.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/08/22/history-of-the-pack-first-days.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
