<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>[&quot;Wolfpack Alliance&quot;]</title>
    <description>Legendary Alliance in PixelStarships - a Mobile Sci-Fi MMO Game</description>
    <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://wolfpackpss.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 13:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 13:20:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;25 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Trial And Sentencing Of Prinz&amp;#95;Eugen, pt. 1&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-340&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #340.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trial was presided over by the honorary Gymnasiarch and Master of Games, known simply as Xin. Justice Pro Tem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A trial of this magnitude was unheard of. The charges for war crimes were unprecedented. That there could be a crime greater than the widespread destruction and wholesale slaughter of war was unthinkable.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was not a trial in any conventional sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were no laws over the crimes for which the party was being accused. There was no pretext for deciding between which of a captain’s actions could be praised as clever ingenuity. Or denounced for gross and inhumane conduct unbecoming of a starship captain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was not even an existing framework by which a judicial body could hold a trial and make a ruling.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xin was the closest thing to a neutral party that could be found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was the directing voice behind the leading ship and weapons manufacturer in the galaxy. Hailed by some as a technological savant, whose innovations had revolutionized the art of ship operations and interstellar conflict. But by others, he was seen as a wartime profiteer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His company brand was known by name: SavySoda.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xin was not an appointed judge. It was not a title he would have ever chosen to aspire to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a duty bestowed upon him when the accused party was unceremoniously dumped on his doorstep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xin had never sat in deliberation over the guilt or innocence of another man. He had never weighed opposing arguments or contradictory statements. He had no way of proving the truth or validity of any substantiated claims or corroborating evidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The culmination of events forcing him into a role of judicial magistrate put a sour taste in his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing on which Xin did agree. The case needed to be settled quickly and decisively. It was bad for business.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a trial of opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone had a point of view. Everyone took a side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no judgment Xin could make that would appeal to all parties. Or that would not result in a loss towards his company’s future revenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how he ruled, he would be hated and despised for that ruling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was not a soul in the galaxy who had not already formed their own conviction towards the accused. Without bias, there could be no jury of peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xin would rule over the case with undisputed authority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for his service towards justice, he would be reviled with uninhibited and universal loathing.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would be decided here was not just the judgment of one man. What was to be (would be) decided &lt;here&gt; was what would be the honorable and accepted practices for all future engagements of war.&lt;/here&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And how &lt;severely&gt; any crimes of war would be judged, whether or not (regardless of whether) that crime was defined by law /(it was a crime defined by law / regardless of how loosely that crime was defined by law).&lt;/severely&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There would be no heroes here.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/12/31/history-pf-the-pack-prinz-eugen-pt-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/12/31/history-pf-the-pack-prinz-eugen-pt-1.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;22 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lord Of The Undead&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-291&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #291.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist022_Gnasher_01.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist022_Gnasher_01&quot; title=&quot;Gnasher quote&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Will you step into my parlor?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher met ButHow at the docking hatch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He cut an imposing figure, standing against the dark interior of his ship. He wore a heavy fur cloak over a steel chest plate. The metal was embellished with flames along the bottom and hands stretching upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow was dressed in formal uniform. Belt. Buttons. Buckles. Hat under his arm. And proudly on his sleeve, an emblem of his alliance, the Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher cast his cloak off one shoulder and displayed the battle insignia on his own arm: a human skull.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Please, make yourself comfortable,” Gnasher gestured toward a chair at the end of the table. “May I offer you wine?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The room was lit in candlelight. Red heavy drapes hung from the ceiling and walls. Above the mantle place stood a large mirror, ornately framed with gold filigree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh yes, thank you,” ButHow seated himself comfortably in the rich satin cushion. “I hear you were recently promoted to Wolf Lord. Congratulations, captain. That is not a commission that could have been easily earned. Certainly not without friends.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher smiled as he selected a bottle from the cabinet, “Then you are unfamiliar with Wolfpack. ‘Friends’ would not be the right word.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How would you call it?”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher poured the wine. The liquid was thick and dark. He could see only a hint of red through the glass when he held it up to the candlelight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One does not broach the topic of betrayal by asking toward the relations of the other’s allegiance. The very process of analyzing it would only work towards reinforcing those bonds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher did ButHow a courtesy and ignored the question.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A thought has been plaguing my mind since your first communique,” Gnasher said, seguing the conversation. “What do we fight for, you and I? Certainly for our alliances. You for the Elder Drivers. I for Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But what do we gain by our warfare against each other? You expand your borders into our territory. We encroach on your space in return. You attack our transports for gas and minerals. We attack yours. You destroy our ships. We rebuild those ships and then retaliate against yours….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What is it all for?”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow paused to consider the question, “I see you and I have been thinking along the same line. It is the reason that I asked to meet with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Were we younger and wiser, we would have chosen more profitable careers in these times of conflict. Such as ship builders or weapons manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But you and I, these trades are not for us. We are starship captains. Our trade is war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I understand your question, it is not why do we fight? For fighting is in our blood. Rather, it is why do we fight each other? When there are more profitable empires we could battle and plunder together.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher swirled the wine in his glass. So profit was the angle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had to admit it was well-spoken, assuming their commonalities and voicing a foreseeable shared interest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher raised his glass to ButHow in salute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow nodded in acknowledgment.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher spoke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am familiar of a strategy of the Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To bolster the ranks of another alliance, pushing out less powerful but more loyal ships, to clear room for themselves. And then abandoning that alliance at their hour of need and leaving them that much weaker than before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Such I have witnessed at the hands of your alliance against the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet during the Sushi Wars. It was a clever move to topple the once proud empire.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow beamed. At both the apparent compliment and cunning deception.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher continued.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When you speak then of fighting together, I can only assume that you mean fighting among the ranks of the Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“For having witnessed such a ploy, Wolfpack would never allow ships once loyal to the Elder Drivers to join its ranks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And so your proposal is not to join me in my alliance, but that I join you among yours. For profit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow nodded his head in agreement, “As you say, it is so.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher bowed his head thoughtfully, then stood from the table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have made some improvements to the deployment of my boarding crew. I would be humbled to share them with you and get your feedback. It would be a show of good faith between us in any consideration towards a future pact.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I would be honored to look them over,” ButHow responded.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher pulled back one of the drapes to reveal a winding staircase that led down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cold wind blew up from below, wrapping itself caressingly around them. ButHow could see a faint light around the bend, reaching up from the bottom of the staircase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Please, after you,” Gnasher said to his guest.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thick cobwebs swayed overhead among the rafters and arches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old wooden boards creaked eerily beneath their feet, as they wound their way down the staircase. When they reached the bottom, Gnasher lifted one of the torches from its sconce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long shadows stretched down the corridor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The torchlight did not extend far into the darkness. Oozes of black shadow slithered down the cracks of the floors and walls. Seeping toward the disturbance of light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A strange scratching noise could be heard in the distance.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow hesitated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Perhaps we should return. My crew may grow anxious over my absence. I told them I would not be gone long….” &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher stopped and raised an eyebrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You fear the dark? Or that which cannot be seen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What does your fear speak of the courage of the Elder Drivers? How would I interpret that fear to reflect their resolve on the battlefield?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher looked at him more significantly, “Who would join such an alliance?”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow gulped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could not report back in failure to acquire a new ally because he could not control his fear. It was just a dark corridor. Nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He lifted his chin and proceeded down the hall.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resemblance of the ship’s interior to a dark castle was unnerving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First the richly furnished parlor. Then the wooden staircase and cobwebs. And now even the cool air rising off the stones of the floors and walls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stone facade covered a steel hull. Gnasher’s ship was no less impenetrable than any other class 10 ship. But the similarity of its interior to a dark haunting castle was chilling.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher stopped at a heavy door set in the wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strange scratching noise that had been echoing down the hallway came from the other side of this door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow felt a chill run up his spine.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ve assembled them from all over the galaxy,” Gnasher said as he grabbed the handle. “They are quite sturdy and make for excellent boarders. I think you may even recognize a few faces….”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher pulled on the handle. The heavy steel door groaned painfully as it swung on its hinges. As the door opened, the torchlight flickered across the hunched forms of figures shuffling in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow could see the stained and faded emblems of Elder Drivers on tattered sleeves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Brains…. brains….”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher shoved him inside, “Say hello to your new crewmates.” Then slammed the door shut.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow beat his fist loudly against the metal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You can’t do this! Let me out of here!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher leaned close to the steel door and blew a breath of hot air over its cold surface. Drawing a grid with his finger, he began playing a game of Tic-Tac-Toe against himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Don’t be shy, ButHow. Your new friends have been DYING to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Get it? Zombies? DYING to meet you? Oh my, I really am too much,” Gnasher cackled and wiped a tear from his eye.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For his first move of Tic-Tac-Toe, he placed an X in the bottom left corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do you know what a zombie looks for in a first date?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Brains…. BRAAAIIIINNNS!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That is correct, Zombie! And spoken with such adamance. Hmmmmm, let me try to think up something harder.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher opposed his move in Tic-Tac-Toe with an O in the top left corner. It was one of only three plays that could counter his opener. He really hated when he stumped himself.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Have you heard the one about whether zombies eat food with their fingers?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gnash, please! Gnasher! Nooooooooo!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh ho, you guys really are too good at these! No is the correct answer. They eat the fingers separately.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher placed an X in the center of the Tic-Tac-Toe grid.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stakes were high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher was playing on ButHow’s behalf. As his host, it was the best he could offer him. Since Gnasher had already outwitted him once, he certainly couldn’t trust ButHow to play well enough on his own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Xs won, ButHow would go free and return to his ship unharmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if Os won or it was a stalemate…. Well, a draw always goes to the defender. Eat up zombies.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher placed an O in the top right corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gah! Gnasher kicked the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the only move O could make to stop the Xs from getting three in a row. It was a question of whether O would slip up and place his marker in any of the other remaining squares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Gnasher was not stupid. He would not make such an obvious mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were no moves now that would not end in a stalemate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher wiped the game away furiously. He could really be a sore loser.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wild pounding against the door slowly began to fade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well ButHow, it has been fun, but I’m afraid I must go. Maybe we can have dessert later, after I blow up your ship. Let’s say around ATE o’clock?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher howled throatily. Chortling with laughter, “ATE o-clock? Really? I crack myself up!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He turned on his heel and walked away. The flickering torchlight receded with him down the hall, as his laughter echoed madly over the quiet sounds of munching.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Captain on the bridge”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher swept his fur cloak over one shoulder and sat down hard in the captain’s chair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow was no hapless fly in a spider’s web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gnasher knew his game before he ever set foot on his ship. He was offended that ButHow had even considered him as someone who might be receptive to such a preposterous idea. That he, a senior officer of Wolfpack, could be persuaded so easily to join the Elder Drivers. As if he would ever leave the pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ButHow was a spider. He had just found himself caught in a much bigger wolf’s mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least the zombies seemed to be enjoying what he brought to the table. Gnasher snickered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Load the missiles and fire up the lasers. Let’s see how well his ship fights without a captain.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist022_Gnasher_02.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist022_Gnasher_02&quot; title=&quot;Gnasher's zombies&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/11/23/history-of-the-pack-lord-of-undead.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/11/23/history-of-the-pack-lord-of-undead.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;21 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Heart Of Man&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrqtarsis-hunterbrstardate-280&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Qtarsis, Hunter.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #280.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beauty is mysterious as well as terrible. God and the devil are fighting there, and the battlefield is the heart of man.&lt;br /&gt;
-Fyodor Dostoevsky, The Brothers Karamazov&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death does not arrive with words of parting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no sweeping overtures. No gentle closing of the eyes or quiet sinking into a peaceful rest. No grand epiphanies. It is not a glimpse into the Unknown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is violent. Immediate. Terrifying. Personal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death is the final judgment over life’s greatest presumption: that it had a right to live.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis looked around his ship. They were all dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Male Nurse on the floor of the reactor. His hands clutched around his throat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roborob and Rocky had boarded the enemy vessel, but their comms had gone silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cannon battery was a slaughter. Most of the crew had rushed there. In a desperate attempt to patch the hull and thwart incoming fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visiri&lt;br /&gt;
Tomas&lt;br /&gt;
Invader&lt;br /&gt;
Cara&lt;br /&gt;
Verunus&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All dead.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Jessica was dying too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her pupils unfocused. Her eyes wild with terror. Fighting for every last breath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis held her in his arms. Helpless.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another barrage of enemy fire wracked the hull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would only be a matter of time before he joined his crew as well. He looked out the observation window on the enemy ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masonobu of Clan Zaki. Former brother-in-arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clan Zaki who had been his home.&lt;br /&gt;
Clan Zaki who sold their honor.&lt;br /&gt;
Clan Zaki who now murdered his crew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis’ eyes burned red.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was an exile of the Sushi Wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Clan Zaki had pawned out their top ships with the other great alliances, to join Sushi Train and overthrow the S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet, Qtarsis found himself abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He walked the corridors and hub centers of the once bustling Zaki star port. Deserted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He checked the docks and moorings for their ship leaders. Empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He undocked his ship and circled the perimeter for one last look at a place he had called home. Alone.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Альянс — твоя семья.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alliance is your family.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis had been a proud member of Clan Zaki. He felt the sting of their desertion cut deep.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the galactic channels, he heard of one alliance that had set themselves apart from the Sushi Wars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One alliance that had closed its ranks. Lending no significant support to either side. Neither Sushi Train, nor the proud S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One alliance that stood together like a rock, despite the winds of chaos that swept around it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a time of uncertain allegiances, Wolfpack had distinguished themselves by a simple declaration of solidarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solidarity. It was a word that spoke powerfully to Qtarsis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had found a new home. He would not arrive empty-handed.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had learned of a hidden research facility in Zaki space. Satellite 16. For the Development of Advanced Neuro-Cybernetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was headed by a Dr. Sera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She held multiple PhDs in neuroscience, kinesiology, and robotics. She was the resident expert on cybernetic technology and focused her research in the area of prosthetics. To replace severed or amputated human limbs with new and augmented robotic counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere along the course of her studies and experimentation though, she went mad.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With her numerous breakthroughs and the rapid improvements she was making towards enhanced technology, Dr. Sera began to view the human body as inferior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She proceeded immediately into human experimentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working around the clock, she cycled through multiple test subjects to perfect her design. Captives she had purchased from a slave market now thriving on the disfranchised of war. Indentured. Unwilling. Disposable for the mere fact that their lives were now measured in currency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sera promised that what value life had stripped from them, their deaths would go towards rewarding a higher scientific pursuit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screams that echoed throughout her lab did little to gain their confidence.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The surgical procedures were invasive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sera found that the cybernetics worked more effectively when connected to the brain through the central nervous system. Nerves would be encased by robotic limbs and fused with the metal appendages like a wire plugging into a circuit board.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The procedure for an amputated subject was to stimulate cellular regeneration of the missing nerves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The procedure for an unamputated subject was to carefully expose the nerves by cutting away any surrounding tissue. Then discard the rest like an unwanted growth.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of the necessity to work with the nerve fibers directly and uninhibited, Dr. Sera did not use anesthetics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pain was excruciating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heightened sensitivity of an exposed nerve is tremendous. Something as innocuous as a breath of air could trigger instant shock or nausea. If the stimuli was severe enough, it could even cause immediate cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her lab echoed with screams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sera grew accustomed to the sound. She familiarized it to the relief a patient may feel after extracting a painful molar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such was how she viewed the extremities of the human body. As deformities to be removed. And replaced with superior technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She called it “The Cleansing”.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of the secrecy of the facility, Qtarsis only knew of it as a center for cybernetic advancement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was unaware of the details of its research, the unethical nature of its progress, the name of its head scientist, or the state of her mental decay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the mass exodus of Clan Zaki to Sushi Train, he thought it unlikely that the station would be manned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he invaded its facility, intent on stealing their research as a pledge of loyalty to Wolfpack, Qtarsis was as surprised to see Dr. Sera as she was him. Hunched over her operating table. Wearing a leather butcher’s apron. With a scalpel in hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her surprise though quickly turned to anger at his interruption, and she charged Qtarsis with the scalpel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blaster fire singed the air.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The look of rage on Dr. Sera’s face froze into a comical grimace as she looked down. A black spot slowly swelled outward on her leather apron, darkening the place where her heart had been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She fell forward facedown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis found himself staring down the crackling point of a hand blaster, now aimed at him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessica, The Raven.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had heard of her only in legend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She flew a pirate ship called The Liberator. She was infamous for attacking slave traders, robbing them of their profit, and releasing their captives to freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her crew consisted of three Visiri Capt’ns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were reformed slavers. Hard men. They fought to reclaim their self-honor aboard her ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessica had a piercing gaze. She could measure the mettle of a man over how he responded while being held at gunpoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any slavers, who genuinely wished to repent of their misdeeds after their ship had been destroyed, were welcome among her crew. Any who did not, were welcome out the airlock.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis held out his hands, “Thank you. I owe you debt of gratitude. I was waiting for fork to go with knife.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ha! Jessica lowered her hand blaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had been pursuing a lead on a buyer whose slaves had been mysteriously disappearing, which led her here to Satellite 16.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once Qtarsis became aware of the type of research they were conducting, he knew Wolfpack would want no part of it. Neither for its findings, nor the butchery that had furthered its discoveries. No one would.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He and Jessica rounded up what captives they could and rigged the station with thermal detonators. Set to blow the moment they departed.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their’s would become a lasting partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis spoke with no small disdain of the Sushi Wars, or the slave trade that was being fueled by its devastation. When he discussed Wolfpack and his intent to ally with them, Jessica offered to join as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They dropped off the released captives at the next free trade port. Most were too debilitated or too far gone mentally to be of use aboard a starship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But one proved able-bodied. And anxious to redeem himself against his aggressors. Roborob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis and Jessica pooled their resources, sold their ships, and upgraded to a class 7 alien warship.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they flew into Wolfpack space, Qtarsis had not thought what to expect. Whatever his subconscious may have conceived, it was certainly not this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack was arrayed for war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their black warships floated heavily across space. Bristling with armament.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dark. Dangerous. Menacing.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis pledged his oath of loyalty to Wolfpack. The words were grim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lord Commander WarWolff draped a heavy fur cloak across Qtarsis’ shoulders. Pronouncing him the rank of Hunter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff scowled at him under his brow. Glaring with black eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daring him to fail.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An explosion in the lower reactor jarred Qtarsis back to the present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His crewmates were dead. Their bodies littered around the ship. Jessica in his arms. Looking upwards. Gulping for air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The enemy Masonobu continued pounding his hull with heavy fire.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something stirred inside Qtarsis. It was quiet at first, but it slowly increased in volume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an old song. Proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sang of a fatherland that no longer existed. On a planet that was no longer habitable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sang of seas and icecaps. Woods and fields. It sang of patriotism and glory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proud words full of conviction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It surged through Qtarsis and filled him with strength.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He bellowed out the words powerfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It filled his lungs and filled the air. It echoed down the elevator shafts. Bounced off the walls. Surged through the reactors and systems like an electric current.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full of energy and power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His voice, loud with song, reverberated throughout the hull.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis stood and walked to the plasma cannon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He tore open the side panel with bare fingers and ripped out the power conduit connecting it to the main reactor. He tore open the panel of the auxiliary laser and thrust the detached power line, now sparking in his hand, into the secondary outlet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crackles of electricity arced around Qtarsis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His voice swelled with fury. Words leaping from his throat louder and louder.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He grabbed the controls of the laser and thrust them to full power. His voice bellowing mightily. Overloading the system and firing a continuous beam that cut across the entire length of the enemy hull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was more power than the laser could harness and the gun casing exploded. Throwing Qtarsis back against the far wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preliminary explosions ruptured along the enemy ship where the beam breached its length, before the vessel detonated in one final seismic explosion.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Farewell Masonobu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Мы стали врагами не по своей воле.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only war makes us enemies.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qtarsis pulled himself along the floor and propped himself up beside Jessica.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He leaned against her. Their arms touching shoulder to shoulder. Her lifeless eyes staring blankly on their last victory together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the smoldering ship of Masonobu sunk out of view, Qtarsis shared with her in one last gaze. Looking out the observation window. Across the glittering canvas of space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Чем ночь темней, тем ярче звезды. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The darker the night, the brighter the stars.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist021_Qtarsis.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist021_Qtarsis&quot; title=&quot;Qtarsis&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Apollon Maykov, untitled poem (1878) &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/11/14/history-of-the-pack-heart-of-man.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/11/14/history-of-the-pack-heart-of-man.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;20 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Songs Of Love And Battle For The First Wolf Victor&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-273&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #273.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara gazed out the observation window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last weeks had been bloody. They were always bloody at the end of a cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top ace captains of every fleet raged ruthless war on each other. Brazenly trespassing onto other fleet territories. Preying on weaker ships. Plundering resources and trophy souvenirs to adorn their hulls. Settling disputes at the end of a gun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deep blood feuds were born.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intergalactic news recognized the top three captains. Those whose warships were most garishly decorated in the trophies of their defeated enemies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1st. thunder_kiss_65&lt;br /&gt;
2nd. 七宇&lt;br /&gt;
3rd. Prinz_Eugen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All were of the fleet Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All featuring their own pictcasts. Weapons unholstered. Teeth grinning broad-toothed smiles. Standing triumphant over the smoldering ruins of some unfortunate captain. Like whalers leaning proudly against their harpoons. Their biggest catch hooked and pulled up alongside their ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contemptuous. Flagrant. Cruel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a galaxy thirsty for war.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having routed Victrix Mortalis, Wolfpack made a good standing for themselves. Solidly securing their own foothold in the galaxy. They were surpassed only by the Dark Matter Heroes and Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack even gave a strong account of themselves among the top captains. One of the pack’s new recruits, OliveOyl, placed herself in 5th. Despite being hospitalized after a ruptured bulkhead smashed into her shoulder and shattered her arm. Lord Commander WarWolff was close behind at 8th.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack was even strong enough to send aid to Dark Matter Heroes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following friendly discussions between Caxy and one of the leaders of Dark Matter Heroes, Citizenband, they reached an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RollFizelBeef, Myke, SCVsUnion, Dan_the_man181, and JeffLA would all go over to lend a hand to their new allies. Helping them fend off repeated incursions by the Elder Drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caxy even brought his own ship out of port and dusted off the console to look over omega pack during the last days of the cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an exciting time for Wolfpack. One of growing power. They were strong enough now to use their own fleet as leverage to determine the fate of the galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack would soon make a reckoning.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara had planted her ship along one of Wolfpack’s borders. Protecting their fleet with a bristling armament of firepower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting up a defensive perimeter in space is not easy. Ships are isolated, often light years apart, and can be scanned from a sector away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to escape a battle usually ends in catastrophe. There is a split second before warp jump kicks in where your ship is completely exposed to enemy fire. If the enemy aims a well-placed shot at the warp drive, then kablooey! The warp field collapses around the hull, crushing your ship within it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even sending a distress signal is pointless. Help could never reach you in time.  The best you can hope for is that someone sends a shop-vac and good cleanup crew. Or vultures to pick up the scraps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Space battles are fatalistic. Either your ship survives. Or it becomes a trophy adorning another ship’s wall.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara was attacked first by Cloggster of Clan Zaki. It was a brutal exchange of weapons, but Sumara came out on top. She left the wracked hulk of his ship smoking not far from her position. A warning against further adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she was attacked by 麦道大牛牛.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then by Quansei, Mdff8, and KuKu桑 .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Single-handedly, she defeated them all. Lining the blackened husks of their broken ships in front of her. Like heads mounted on the pickets of a castle wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of warding off would-be attackers, the more victories she accumulated then the fiercer she was attacked. A mighty fire-belching dragon that every captain intent on proving his valor was keen to slay.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara was a fierce fighter. One of Wolfpack’s best. Her succession of repeated defenses won her recognition across the galaxy, claiming her top prize in the Wolfpack’s Alpha Wolf Contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as earning her honorable mention in the Pillaging Scourge &amp;amp; Looting Lunatics starlog contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was a legend.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara looked out the observation window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her ship orbited the planet Xeanus in the border sector. A white star shone around the edge of the planet’s sphere. Catching the dunes of desert gold along its surface, under the aqua blue atmosphere. It was breathtaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She hadn’t forgotten why she had become a starship captain. Launching through the atmosphere at speeds upwards of Mach 23. The galaxy opening before her. Like walking out of a cave through a waterfall. Flying among the stars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invigorating. Untethered. Free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just look at that view.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, letters have arrived from fleet headquarters.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara leaned back in the captain’s chair. Kicking her feet up on the console and luxuriously sinking in the soft fur rug draped across the back. She grabbed the hip flask from her belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roborob set the letters down in a neat stack next to her heel. Careful to not make eye contact. Focusing on some undefined point just over her shoulder. Deliberately looking somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara watched his eyes. Swirling the liquid around in her flask. Sloshing some unidentifiable object around within. Then she took a swig.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roborob blanched visibily, “I’ll leave you to it, sir.” He saluted, then speedily exited the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara smirked. The joke never got old.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was much loved in the pack. As well as among other fleets in the galaxy. Winning herself the nickname Smelzy among her closest friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was aware of her growing popularity. But having championed the intergalactic contests, her fame was reaching unprecedented proportions. Now she was receiving fan letters of undying love and loyalty from the pack?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hmmmm, poetry. The cat sat on a mat inside a vat with a rat. This should prove interesting….”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smelzy oh Smelzy&lt;br /&gt;
Your eau de toilette is smelly&lt;br /&gt;
Offspring grow in your belly&lt;br /&gt;
Just don’t show it on the telly&lt;br /&gt;
–Gnasher&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dread Wolf Sumara&lt;br /&gt;
Likes stickers and dirty jokes&lt;br /&gt;
She’ll beat your chump ass&lt;br /&gt;
–SCVsUnion&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dreadnought Sumara&lt;br /&gt;
All shall yield to Sumara&lt;br /&gt;
Nothing shall stop her&lt;br /&gt;
–Captain Kainus&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara, badass&lt;br /&gt;
Can you catch her? Better run&lt;br /&gt;
Bloody feasts await.&lt;br /&gt;
–fritz&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drink from me&lt;br /&gt;
Lips of red&lt;br /&gt;
Moonlight on the pale skin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Live for life&lt;br /&gt;
Love through death&lt;br /&gt;
Drink from me an eternal kiss&lt;br /&gt;
–ArchNadeom&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smelzy the Wolf Lord&lt;br /&gt;
Counting her bux and laughing. &lt;br /&gt;
BUX BUX BUX BUX BUX&lt;br /&gt;
–SCVsUnion&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Valkyries cries&lt;br /&gt;
Songs of war&lt;br /&gt;
The victors stories&lt;br /&gt;
Striding amongst the pack&lt;br /&gt;
They howl in triumph&lt;br /&gt;
Sumara’s bloody glory&lt;br /&gt;
–WarWolff&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Опали враги,&lt;br /&gt;
Как осенние листья.&lt;br /&gt;
Восходит звезда.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the enemies fell down&lt;br /&gt;
Like the autumn leaves.&lt;br /&gt;
The star is rising.&lt;br /&gt;
–Qtarsis&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara is beautiful,&lt;br /&gt;
she’s a defence machine,&lt;br /&gt;
better have a bridge,&lt;br /&gt;
all she’ll blow you away&lt;br /&gt;
–xEEVEEx&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A line of smoke rising&lt;br /&gt;
Sumara is reigning ov’r ashes&lt;br /&gt;
She rules over the sky&lt;br /&gt;
–Smores182&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shark shark shark shark&lt;br /&gt;
SUMA SUMA SUMA Oli&lt;br /&gt;
Shark shark shark shark shark&lt;br /&gt;
–OliveOyl&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I follow Smelzy&lt;br /&gt;
By her trailzy&lt;br /&gt;
You cannot failzy&lt;br /&gt;
To recognize the smellzy&lt;br /&gt;
–Gnasher&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suma in the Fall,&lt;br /&gt;
Sweet grapes dripping from a glass,&lt;br /&gt;
Enemies cower&lt;br /&gt;
–Machiel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist020_Sumara_Poems.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist020_Sumara_Poems&quot; title=&quot;Sumara&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/10/04/history-of-the-pack-songs-of-love.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/10/04/history-of-the-pack-songs-of-love.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;17 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Mind's Grand Arc, pt. 1&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;warwolff-lord-commanderbrstardate-271&quot;&gt;WarWolff, Lord Commander.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #271.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The void had swallowed him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Utter darkness stretched out before him, so inky and black that it almost had form in the mind’s eye. He had always wondered how complete nothingness was able to bear such crushing pressure on the mind, on the soul. Eyes shut tight against the weight, he exhaled slowly and opened them with purpose. Try as he might, no sight nor sound reached him. There was only this smothering world of nothingness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper of the Histories, Sage, Fury, and Dreadnought. All these titles and glory bestowed upon him, but only one thought ravaged his racing mind, “I must go. This must end!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was a Wolf Lord. One of the highest ranking members in WolfPack. Battle-hardened and draped in honours. Yet none of his achievements could hasten his release from this void. He was bound to this fate. But he knew that it would not be for long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had been passed an important piece of intel only a short while ago, that if acted upon quickly could garner himself and his beloved pack even more power and leverage in the galaxy. It was vital that this opportunity not be wasted. Time was ticking by and each second was a chance lost. He had to go. He had to act now! With that thought he raised his arms out, tilted his head back, and let loose a raging howl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The END!” he roared. With this simple yet bold proclamation, his world exploded into light and chaos.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Grande Odeum was still awash in a cacophony of cheers, clapping, and howls from the multitudes of adoring fans, as ArchNadeom descended the raised dais. He stopped and turned for one final salute before he exited the main stage. The theatre was well over capacity this night. Many of the visiting dignitaries mingled shoulder to shoulder on the standing-room-only platforms with the Pack’s warrior poets, whom so loved a good ballad. His gaze fell down past the platforms to the seating bowl below. They stretched back so far he could barely make out the figures, still standing in applause under the bright spot lights and nova flashes that now burned away the darkness of the void.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well done Arch,” a hand clasped his shoulder warmly. WarWolff’s deep voice had a hint of levity in it as he spoke, “He’ll be proud and honoured.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two gave each other a small nod of acknowledgment and parted ways. There was no need to say more. They were wolves. That simple acknowledgment spoke in words which can’t be spoken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom turned and began making his way through the mass of stagehands and devotees that had gathered backstage to greet him. He was surprised at how well his new epic had been received. Not only on Omega, but throughout the sectors and amongst the varying alliances. The ship docks were filled with sleek, luxurious Proxima starjammers, hundreds of old, worn-out cargo skiffs and sloops, even the large tourist galleons jockeyed for space. And that was only the underground port facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The orbital ports had never seen the likes of the armada that had descended upon Omega, except at times of war. And even then, it could not match the diversity and size of the fleet of capital ships that now secured every available berth. He had word that even the deep space anchorages were running low on docking space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had done well, he chuckled to himself. He knew it would be popular, but hadn’t envisaged just what an impact his writings would have. As he made his way to the back of the theatre, finally free from the small talk, admiration, and glad handing, he glanced up and peered at a holo-vid advertising his reading that evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LORD WOLF SAGE ARCHNADEOM’S rendition of ‘The Ballad of the Last Battle of Caxy’ streamed across the screen. As an image of a massive matte black class 10 Leviathan capital ship, with the Lord Commander’s sigil on the stern, hung in the background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard not to have a hit when you have him to write about. He was much loved and respected by all WolfPack, and even amongst the various alliances that populated the known sectors. Respected, loved, and feared. Few could stand against him and hope to win. Even One Three Tombo of fleet Prestige Worldwide had earned a hard-fought respect for Caxy. And Caxy for him. That was his way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arch caught himself thinking about war stories, old past glories, and then quickly shook them off. With one last glimpse over his shoulder at the clamour, still echoing down through the tall grey halls that were lined with red granite columns the width of a plasma canon, he silently slipped out a freight door and into the night.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He moved across the open courtyard with urgency, but not in haste. The moon had risen above the high polished walls of the Grande Odeum. Spraying its feathery light through the many spires and turrets of the Citadel and across the courtyard like so many white fingers chasing away the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silently, ArchNadeom made his way to the far side, where the stone abruptly ended at the foot of a large automated orbital defence platform. The dark grey metal of the defence station rose up above him. Streaks of moonlight ran straight down the barrels of the plasma cannons and arched across the heads of the point defence missiles, as he made his way around to where the platform met the outer edge of the Citadel wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five hundred feet below the rooftops, the plasma lighting of the capital city brightly glared up at him. He turned and stared up at the bulk of the Citadel that still hung above him, as it climbed up past the Grande Odeum and the other buildings on the third bench. The vast, flat, angular wall sections, made of the same dark grey metal as the defence platforms, rose up and up; only broken by other platforms and the second and primary benches, until it blended into the geography of the cliff wall that supported it all. Higher and higher it rose on the cliff into the sky, metallic yet subdued and dark, until it finally peaked and the great rocky roof of the Wolf’s Head formation arched its maw out and over the whole Citadel some 300 feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Into the mouth of a giant stone wolf,” Arch grinned. The Citadel was old. Very old. Throughout the ages, many additions and upgrades had been made. From the massive zero point energy reactors, sunk a mile below the bedrock, to the gardens and courtyards that flourished everywhere you looked. The Citadel was a place of nature and beauty, but it was also a weapon. Every nook, cranny, and corner, hosting an array of cannons, turrets, and missile defences, made the Citadel one hard target. It had never fallen. The old captains joked that you could crack the planet in two before cracking the Citadel. Looking up in wonder and pride, Arch felt it to be true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quick retinal scan and the heavy door to the defence platform slid open. The smell of old half-eaten protein ration packs and Lupis ale wafted out to greet him. He was just about to enter when he was stopped by a familiar voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Always love the stories but hated the attention, hey Arch?” The words were blunt but filled with merriment, “Can I come this time?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His head slightly drooped. Without turning, he quietly spoke, “You know that I like to operate alone. My whisperers don’t trust anyone and they spook easily… And this is one time that I cannot afford to make a mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He slowly pivoted on his heel and his friend came into view, “I promise next time you can fly with me, but not this time Sumara.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He squared up to her, looking her up and down. The neck of her great Wolf Lord’s cloak brushed up against her cheeks and fell away off her shoulders, flowing back behind her legs and revealing a small woman in formal battle attire. She had really gone all out for the nights festivities, he mused. She wore bluish-grey armour plates, strategically covering a dark red Coridian groot leather tunic, and leggings that were a good match for the formfitting black knee-high boots, slashed with more armoured shin-plates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was quite a sight to behold. Intimidating and deadly, while small and beautiful. The WolfPack’s red-toothed Fury belt adorned her waist, the Vanquisher gold-worked bracers wrapped her forearms, and most striking, the black-and-silver crisscross chest harness that denoted she was the elite of the elite. She was a Dreadnought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom’s hand went up instinctively and rested on his own black-and-silver chest harness. How many ships had fallen before them collectively? How many lives and glories cut short by just these two Wolfpack Dreadnoughts?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question flittered from his mind as Sumara spoke, “I understand Arch.” She murmured, not making any attempt to hide her displeasure and disappointment, “You must do what you must, but know that I have your back if you need it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I always know you do. And I you. But I must decline this time. This is far too delicate an affair to chance anything.” To be completely honest, he wouldn’t have minded some backup. He did not know what to expect on this mission. Such was his lot in life. He had weathered all challenges previously. This time would be no different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Take care of yourself,” she beamed and wrapped him in a short, fierce embrace. She released him, then started backing away with a smile and nod. He nodded, turned, and passed through the doorway into the gloom of the defence platform, when he heard Sumara whisper, “Be careful when dealing with him. He’s the only one I know of that has reliable transit maps of the Aulux sector.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom spun around, his black fur cloak casting a vast arc swirling around him,” How did….?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest of the sentence hung in his mouth, as he stared across a vast empty courtyard. There was no sign of Sumara, or that she had ever been there. He glanced around, straining for some sign of her, but it was not to be. He shook his head in wonderment. Then threw his head back and burst into laughter.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The air whooshed around him as the levels passed. Plasma lights blinked in and out of existence through the large metal frame of the cargo elevator, as it picked up speed descending down, down, and further down into the Citadel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom often used the defence platform munitions elevators to navigate the warren of buildings and people in the fortress. When not at war, these shafts were not in use. One could get from the top of the Citadel to the reactor cores in a fraction of the time of the main transportation hubs, and without anyone noticing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the cores were not his destination this day. This day, he was heading to WolfPack’s subterranean starport. A sprawling network of caverns, protected from orbital bombardment hundreds of feet beneath the bedrock of the surface. It housed the berths of capital ships, destroyers, and frigates of the Wolfpack fleet. And his own beloved ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, best if no one noticed him leaving this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how had Sumara known? His mind raced, struggling for answers that did not come. He had received the encrypted message through the neural implant of his personal comm array aboard his ship, The Harvester. He hadn’t spoken to anyone of it, not even the Lord Commander. So how did she know about the Aulux sector?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The munitions elevator growled as it slowed its descent and eventually stopped. The mesh door slid up with a screech of metal on metal and he peered out, across the massive rocky interior of the fleet’s starport. The port was quiet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A handful of automated SCVs flew around the great hulk of warships. The glow of their cutting lasers illuminated sections of the battle-scarred hulls like electric bumblebees. But otherwise there was little movement or signs of life. Perfect, he thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He wound his way through the starport. Over walkways anchored into the stone walls of the caverns, through filling stations, and past docked space tugs and ammo dumps, until he came to a smaller cavern that branched off the main port. As he rounded the corner, the sleek, glistening, black-and-red hull of The Harvester rose up in front of him. Deadly lances of missile tubes and cannons sprouting from the sides, auto turret and ACL barrels bristling like a centurion’s helmet, and large round communication pods hung off the aft like a clutch of eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was a good ship. Solid and dependable. A captain couldn’t ask for more. And yet, many wondered why he hadn’t moved up to a capital class vessel? All captains as decorated as him should have a capital ship surely, and yet ArchNadeom flew a class 9 destroyer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His reasons were simple and they were his own. He was not only the Wolfpack historian, but he was also their chief information officer. As such, he often benefitted from the lower visibility that a smaller ship granted. If a destroyer pulled into a foreign port, people didn’t pay much mind, thinking it was a routine patrol or scouting mission. But when a capital ship transited into a system… Well, everyone and their dog knew about it. Which drew far too many eyes and questions for his line of work. He liked working behind the scenes and the shadows suited him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another bonus was that many capital ship captains, on seeing the smaller class 9 destroyer, were inclined to think that this was a soft target and easy plunder. Typically finding out, right before their reactors went critical and they themselves were vented out into the cold black of space, that this was not the case. He wasn’t a Dreadnought because he was easy meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hello old girl,” he chimed. A smile reaching his eyes, as he moved up the gang plank and into the main airlock,”It’s time to get to work.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As he entered the bridge of The Harvester, his first mate Rocky greeted him with a low measured, “Captain on deck.” For a rock, he was quite the intellectual himself, but would never admit it openly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom unclasped his fur cloak and dropped it from his shoulders. Removing his Dreadnought harness, he flung it casually into an unoccupied terminal chair. Followed by his red-toothed Fury belt, Sage Wolfhead medallion, along with all the other trappings of lordship and rank. He pulled an old, worn, leather trader’s vest over a simple black wool shirt, and slumped down in the large captain’s chair in the center of the bridge. Looking much the vagabond and less the esteemed sage of just hours ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Jessica, fire up the comms array. Protocol 119. All shadow channels. Run secured deep encryption through main holo display,” he barked. “Lock it down and give me the bridge.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His crew filed out of the bridge without a word, as the blue lines of the holo screen coalesced in front of him and gained form. Side screens flared into life and data started pouring in as the comm arrays whirled, drawing more and more energy, and steadily reaching full power. A deep, resonating hum vibrated through the main keel of the ship. Through the walls and bulkheads, into the bridge, up the body of the captain’s chair, and into his back and arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some very smart people had built the large, customized array that channeled all detectable communications in the sector through his main terminal. He thanked them silently. The power the array drew was enormous and tasked the fusion reactors to their limits. But with it, he could track every conversation and all data that flowed between every ship, civilization, and colony. He had it all laid out before him in streaming lines of data. Immense quantities of information waiting to be gazed upon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He did not know how Sumara had known of the Aulux sector. It was more commonly known as the Furrow. A dark and dangerous stretch of space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long ago, it had been the home of an advanced alien civilization that had destroyed itself in a cataclysmic civil war. The best scientists of the day were still trying to work out what matter of weapons were used that could leave behind rends in space-time thousands of years later. These floating rends would rip a ship into base atoms, if contacted, and were not detectable by any known means. That, and the widely fluctuating gravimetric fields, made the Furrow a warren of death and mayhem. Any sane captain, and most insane captains, would avoid it at all costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the Furrow was also a realm of lost ruins and advanced technology, and that always drew in a special breed. The smugglers, the criminals, the looters and scavengers, the down-on-their-luck looking for a last chance against all odds to make one payday that would set the course of their lives. It was diving into madness and chaos, and that’s where he needed to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Into the Furrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was only one person he knew of, who had their fingers burrowed into the secrets of the sector even deeper than he. Only one that had the resources to map out a credibly safe transit map and get him to where he needed to go. His nemesis and rival in intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They had often worked in opposition to each other. Playing their own pieces in a great game, and even coming to blows ship-to-ship on the odd occasion. Once speaking of him, WarWolff had made an offhand joke about his intelligence capabilities, referring to him as ‘Mr Universe’, since he was everywhere, while being nowhere. ArchNadeom had not laughed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He sat sourly looking at the holo screen, then angrily punched in a series of commands on his chair’s console. The screen lit up with a data transmission signal and he waited. His face hard but composed, until a solid tone sounded that the signal was in the clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He loathed what he was now forced to do. He would have to acquiesce to his great rival and ask for a favour, “Hello, Vlad.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist017_ArchNadeom_Pt1(by_WarWolff).PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist017_ArchNadeom_Pt1(by_WarWolff)&quot; title=&quot;ArchNadeom&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/10/02/history-of-the-pack-the-minds-grand-arc-pt1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/10/02/history-of-the-pack-the-minds-grand-arc-pt1.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;16 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Struggle For Power, pt. 3&amp;#58; Heroes Honored&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-264&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #264.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Snow gathered on the branches. Casting shadows under the moonlight. Through the trees. Fields of white dusted in glittering blue.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff placed a hand against an old wood circling the grove.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could feel the coarsness of its trunk. The cuts in its bark and dried sap under his fingers. The stength in its stand, as it towered over him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Elder Circle on Omega.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a deep power here. Ancient. Resonating. Echoing with the howls of old wolves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could hear them through the trees. Feel their energy swell inside him. And something else too. Pride. Wolfpack had done well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff summoned his pack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a solemn meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tall figures standing in the snow. Heavy cloaks hunched over broad shoulders. White flecks of snow catching in their fur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara bundled in her silk rug. _sharky_’s conscience represented in its steel automaton. SCVsUnion flexing the fingers of his guantlet, keeping the joints from seizing in the cold. Oliver standing beside him.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the pack were present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel of the Green Fire&lt;br /&gt;
Deathlord291 the Merciless&lt;br /&gt;
ArchNadeom, Keeper of Records&lt;br /&gt;
fritz of the First Howl&lt;br /&gt;
Seq, Keeper Of The Way&lt;br /&gt;
Hyten, the Sentinel&lt;br /&gt;
Caxy, the All-Father&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CyberWocky&lt;br /&gt;
MizzBlaze&lt;br /&gt;
Librakron&lt;br /&gt;
Voxar&lt;br /&gt;
Skinkrules&lt;br /&gt;
Qtarsis&lt;br /&gt;
Ivydocious&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their breath hit the air in steaming white puffs. Hot. Like snorting hounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their black eyes burning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff stood in the center. Mighty WarWolff. Lord Commander of Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx stood before his commander at attention. The former members of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet standing in a line to his side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RollFizelBeef&lt;br /&gt;
Myke&lt;br /&gt;
Nausicaa&lt;br /&gt;
Gnasher&lt;br /&gt;
Dan_the_man181&lt;br /&gt;
JeffLA&lt;br /&gt;
Sa ok&lt;br /&gt;
Alinea&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx had instructed them ahead of time. They were to dispense of their pearlescent S.Q.U.I.D. cloaks before the ceremony and arrive in simple white garb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They felt naked. Exposed. Surrounded by dark imposing figures. Their hot breath. Their fierce gaze. The tall trees looming over them. Stretching them deeper into their shadows.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff looked to the side and gave Caxy a nod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caxy stepped forward with a bundle of furs in his arms. xEEVEEx stepped from the line and met Caxy at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was xEEVEEx who had drawn the S.Q.U.I.D. expatriates into their ranks. Helping them find a home among Wolfpack. It was xEEVEEx who had called them to the pack’s rescue against Victrix Mortalis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The honors were his to bestow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He picked up a cloak from Caxy’s bundle and draped it over RollFizelBeef’s shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He smiled at his friend. Then gave him a squeeze on the arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one, he draped a fur cloak over each of the former S.Q.U.I.D.s’ shoulders. Giving each a friendly nod, smile, or a touch on the arm.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The depth of the ceremony was powerful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the cloak settled around their shoulders, they could feel the weight of its meaning. The warmth of its fur against the cold. Their own heat swelling within.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No longer did they feel naked or exposed. It was the warmth of the pack surrounding them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They had found a new family. One that recognized their strength. Not only as a pack, but as individuals. And bulstered each other’s strengths with that of their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No longer would they be cast-out. Disbanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No longer would they be alone.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx was proud of his new packmates. Each of them smiling in return. He turned, about to resume his place in line, when WarWolff stopped him. A hand against his shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff gave him a stern look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx faltered. Uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had he missed something? He had performed this ceremony a dozen times before for new packmates. Though not with such formality. Or for such a large audience. But he was sure he hadn’t missed anything. Had he?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff looked to Sumara and gave her a nod.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of Sumara’s fur cloak, she drew forth a great helmet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The metal was glossy black, with a frog-mouth face guard. A plume of horsehair, stark white, flowed long and wild from a spike in the crown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara carried it to WarWolff. Bearing it on the upturned palms of her hands. Holding it outstretched before her. A relic. Reverential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the Helmet of Stodz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stodz the First. Of the days of yore. One of the greatest legends of Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff accepted the helmet from Sumara with a deep bow of his head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He looked at xEEVEEx and gave a significant look down. xEEVEEx took a knee. WarWolff placed the helmet on xEEVEEx’s head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cold metal buzzed to life. Gears whirled and clank shut, fastening the armor in place. Seams lit up and glowed in stripes of an electric lantern blue.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The helmet was alive multi-dimensionally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An alien intelligence entered xEEVEEx’s conscience. Finding new neural paths to synapses in his brain that had long lain dormant. Stimulating them to life. Triggering new thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It could link wormholes. Circumnavigate black holes to the other side of the galaxy. Hide in the folds of space-time, where reality bent in on itself. Establish new contacts. Surprise his enemies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The inner workings of space lay revealed to him.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx stood. Armor plates extended out from the helmet. Clapping down on his shoulders. Down his back. Across his chest. Armoring his arms and legs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx had entered into a symbiotic relationship with the helmet. It would die for xEEVEEx. Protecting its host. Guarding his life with its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It demanded only one thing in return. Loyalty.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A metal rod punched through xEEVEEx’s sternum and latched itself painfully around his heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx understood the implication, should he ever try to take the helmet off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He wondered how Stodz had manipulated the thing.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff patted xEEVEEx on the shoulder. Power with sacrifice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx had given the best of himself for the pack. WarWolff gave the best of the pack to xEEVEEx in return. The circle was closed.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara kicked open a metal container, “Finally! At least we don’t have to worry about the champagne getting warm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry xEEVEEx, I think I can squeeze a tube through that visor of your’s so you can have champagne too. I’ve got PLENTY of experience from my drinking days in Bore-Us-With-Books Academy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ceremony over, it was time for rough-housing and play.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new recruits blended in well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were as full of life and strength as his seasoned wolves. They found a natural harmony with their new packmates. And they brought so much of their own vibrance and knowledge to the pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx had made a great decision bringing them in. WarWolff was proud of them. He was proud of his pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was proud of xEEVEEx.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist016_WarWolffPt3.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist016_WarWolffPt3&quot; title=&quot;xEEVEEx&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/26/history-of-the-pack-heroes-honored.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/26/history-of-the-pack-heroes-honored.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;15 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Struggle For Power, pt. 2&amp;#58; No Plan Survives&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-262&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #262.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a touch on eternity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A pause in the flow of time. A stillness of mind. When a quiet settles in. The senses becoming focused and acute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the little things that did not matter before, suddenly take on a precendence. Colors become brighter. Sound more crisp. Simple words take on a depth of meaning they do not otherwise possess.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff could see the light of the nearby moon. Pouring through the observation window. Touching the ozone in the air and streaming it into rays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could smell the metallic tang of the hull. Taste the adrenaline on his tongue. Feel the coarse fur of his cloak against his cheek.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He sensed something else too. Something not of this place. He felt their hush in the room. A presence just beyond his perception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could not see them, but he knew they were there. As they were always there. At every decisive moment. Nudging. Lifting him back up. Lending their strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ancestors of Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff closed his eyes and gave them a silent nod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Protect my fleet. I have lead them as best I knew how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They fight for the honor of the pack. They would honor you still, though they do not know you. As they have honored me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They are good wolves. Grant them your strength. See them through this day.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff lifted his head and looked out. His gaze falling on the enemy armada before him. Victrix Mortalis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His black eyes glimmered.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 50% power.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fleet responded to WarWolff’s command as if they were part of his ship. Holding formation. Keeping pace with their Lord Commander as if they were marching drill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack moved as one towards the enemy.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 60% power.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no drag in space. No airpockets or turbulence. No resistance to slow acceleration. To set a constant speed in space, you would simply fire the engines once and then turn them off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To leave the engines running at a constant power does not maintain a constant speed. It continues the acceleration. Propelling the ship onward, faster and faster, as it hurtles madly at wildly increasing speeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are limits to speed even in space, but they are measured in the astronomical.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 70% power.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff could feel the ship vibrating beneath him. A humming noise started in the beams and was slowly beginning to echo in the hull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The images on the displays began to blur. The crew strapped themselves in. Fastening their wrists to the terminals to ensure they still pressed the right keys despite the vibrations.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 80% power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, break off formation and halt your advance. Engage the enemy when they come in range. Maintain a tactical retreat.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Orders to an officer were different than those to a capitan. Officers were promoted based on their initiative, ingenuity, and ability to coordinate a squadron of ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff would not be directing this battle from afar. He would be part of the battle. As such, he would only be able to oversee the operations of the fleet to a limited degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would depend on his officers to think independently. To be there. To respond. To act. To make the quick on-the-spot decisions that would be necessary to carry Wolfpack to victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, the orders for an officer had to be in terms of strategy and generalization. Allowing ample room for them to command their squadrons and respond to immediate threats as best they saw fit, while still carrying out their orders.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 90% power.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ slowly began to pull ahead of the fleet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The massive battering ram on the nose of _sharky_’s ship was better suited to close combat. Pulling ahead, he would engage the enemy at the same time as the long-range fire of the rest of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff understood. He was as eagar as his captains to cut his teeth on the enemy. The captains knew their own ships better than he.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would not countermand them. He had entrusted them with that authority. To countermand them would be to discredit himself in a misplacement of trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_ would draw the enemy’s first fire, but that battering ram would serve as much a shield for _sharky_ as it would a ram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Godspeed _sharky_.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines to 100% power.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire ship was rattling. WarWolff grabbed a hold of the frame surrounding the observation window and began digging his fingers into the metal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gun crew, load the 64 inch shells into the cannons. Fire on my command.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Targeting would be choppy, but with the enemy fleet pressed so tightly together he was sure he would hit something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The enemy ship Runningman swelled into range. Its black hull growing larger and larger as they drew closer. Filling most of the crosshairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fire!!”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The twin cannons Krupp and Big Bertha barked powerfully. Belching out two massive shells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big Bertha missed, but Krupp hit the side reactor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the velocity of the projectile added to the already incredible speed of WarWolff’s ship, the shell dimpled into Runningman’s shield and then popped through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It mushroomed against the hull, doubling in size. Buckling the frame inward and then tearing off the whole rear starboard side of the ship.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_’s attack was not as successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He depended on surprise and hitting the enemy broadside, where he would have a much larger target and need to only compensate for minor adjustments in the enemy’s tilt or speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But facing the enemy head-on, the slightest change in direction for either ship could result in him missing completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the last minute, the enemy veered to the right. Just before impact. _sharky_’s battering ram scraped along the side of the enemy ship. Shaving off the enemy’s port-side guns like barnacles under a knife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because Victrix Mortalis had arranged their fleet in such tight formations, they did not leave each other much room to maneuver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the ship veered starboard, he collided into another Victrix Mortalis ship. Jostling again the ships next to them. The rank of ships behind them barrelling on top of them in turn. Side into Side. Above and below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It became a roadblock of broken ships.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CyberWocky had been following close behind _sharky_, riding right on his tail. When the enemy fleet crashed into each other and piled up in front of him, he smashed into the mass of hulls at full-speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without the extra front armor of _sharky_’s battering ram though, CyberWocky’s ship crumpled like a can under a sledgehammer.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Engines at full reverse! Crew, brace for impact!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff’s ship slid to a halt only a stone’s throw away from the enemy fleet. He was close enough to see the enemy crew flung around inside and the smashed systems through their windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A massive explosion rocked WarWolff’s ship from the port side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, our port cannon has been hit. Enemy fire coming from our left flank.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A mighty behemoth of a ship, flying under the name Brook-Lyn, had wheeled her assault onto WarWolff. The wall formation of Victrix Mortalis was slowly pivoting on its center and closing on Wolfpack’s flanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gun crew, focus your cannons on that pile-up of ships. Clear us an opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“xEEVEEx, enemy ships are breaking through our left flank. Hold your position until we can punch through that roadblock.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff’s ship was wracked by another heavy barrage of enemy fire from port-side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“xEEVEEx, respond. Hold that flank!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Commander, SCVsUnion reporting. Lieutenant xEEVEEx split formation and flew off on his own. Voxar and I are fending them off as best we can, but we can’t hold much longer.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx abandoned his post? In the middle of battle?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, our port cannon is destroyed. Our shields can’t withstand that much firepower. The hull is taking damage.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krupp was down. WarWolff would have to save any thought on xEEVEEx until later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Retarget all weapons on the enemy ship Brook-Lyn. Aim for the missle bays. Roborob, Invader and Guan Yu, board the enemy ship. Take down the reactors and slow her rate of fire.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sumara, come in. Redeploy top squadron under Deathlord291 and assume command of left flank. Take Ivydocious with you. Reinforce SCVsUnion and Voxar before our flank collapses.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Aye aye, Commander!”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff looked out the starboard-side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel fought like one possessed. He was engaging three different enemy ships at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A strange green energy was coiling around the beams from Machiel’s lasers. Two of the enemy ships had lit up oddly with green fire that was leaping into space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff didn’t know how long Machiel could sustain that power, but the enemy wasn’t pressing their attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not far from Machiel, MizzBlaze sat eerily quiet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were no visible signs of weapon scoring on the outside of her hull, but her power was clearly dead. No running lights. No engine impulse. Nothing over the radio. She sat stock-still in space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Librakron kept his distance. He looked as wary of Machiel as the enemy was.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Seq and Hyten, take your squadron and form up on our rear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, rejoin the fleet. Extend in a line beyond the rear formation. Do not let that wall close behind us or we are done for!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You have our word, Commander.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victrix Mortalis closed around them like a noose. Enemy ships pounding them from all sides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_sharky_’s ship tilted upward at an awkward angle. Explosions rupturing along his side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A torpedo slipped past Sumara’s shield. Killing her engine and stopping her ship in its tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two well-placed shots took out Machiel’s forward and aft lasers.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff looked on helpless. What had he done? His packmates were dying.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“a-Woooooooo!!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a sound like sunlight through the clouds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx flew out of the nebula with reinforcements on his wings. The powerful officers and ships of the former S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their mighty pearlescent hulls no less diminished by their disbandment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RollFizelBeef&lt;br /&gt;
Myke&lt;br /&gt;
Nausicaa&lt;br /&gt;
Gnasher&lt;br /&gt;
Dan_the_man181&lt;br /&gt;
JeffLA&lt;br /&gt;
Sa ok&lt;br /&gt;
Alinea&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And something else too. The apparitions of wolves. Wolves howling on the flanks of xEEVEEx and the S.Q.U.I.D. warships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack’s ancestors had accepted them. They were S.Q.U.I.D. no more. From this battle to every battle thenceforth, every pack oath, every pack call, they would be wolves.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They tore into the backs of Victrix Mortalis like a hellstorm. Ships disintegrated whole under the awesome volley of their combined firepower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brook-Lyn disengaged from WarWolff to turn and meet the new threat. He took advantage of her distraction to fire a devastating shell from his remaining cannon Big Bertha into her reactor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It triggered a chain-reaction of explosions across the other reactors. Destroying her ship.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx and his new wolf squadron fanned out around the edges. WarWolff rallied his remaining ships. Together, they destroyed the enemy commander Kirkbane before he could mount a defensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The enemy fleet routed. Victrix Mortalis lost its hold of power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack stood in its place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff beamed proudly. A cheer erupted from his ranks. There would be celebration in the coming days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_01.png&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_01&quot; title=&quot;WarWolff defeats Runningman&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_03&quot; title=&quot;WarWolff defeats Brook-Lyn&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_02.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist015_WarWolffPt2_02&quot; title=&quot;WarWolff defeats Kirkbane&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/24/history-of-the-pack-no-plan-survives.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/24/history-of-the-pack-no-plan-survives.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;14 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Struggle For Power, pt. 1&amp;#58; The Great Wolf&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-259&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #259.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff stood on the bridge looking out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could see them. Dark blots against the stars. The hulls of one hundred warships. One thousand guns arrayed against him. The mighty armada of Victrix Mortalis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff stood tall. Hands clasped behind his back. His cloak was heavy. The thick fur cut with many scars. A dangerous glint in his eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His enemies would rue his name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff. Lord Commander of Wolfpack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Great Wolf.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His ship was massive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with standard lasers and missle bays, WarWolff had outfitted the sides of his ship with two enormous projectile artillery cannons. 200 calibre 64 inch batteries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each barrel was 1060 feet long. Three-and-a-half football fields in length. Firing shells that measured 64 inches in diameter. Almost as tall as a man and twice the size of the largest cannon ball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guns were specially encased in a patented 0 Kelvin coolant housing. So much heat was generated per shot that without extra cooling not even the cold vacuum of space could prevent them from melting during operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gun houses, where the crew manned the cannons, were mounted at the rear of the ship. While the barrels were hard-fastened to run along the sides and extend beyond the front. Like two jousting lances held on the back of a horse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cannons only pointed forward and could not maneuver on their own, so they required the ship’s steering to aim. Also, because of the tremendous amount of firepower they packed with each shot, special timing mechanisms had to be built into the engines to counter the powerful force of kickback from each volley and keep the ship steady when firing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff nicknamed them Krupp and Big Bertha.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, the last of Wolfpack has arrived. The fleet is assembled. Awaiting your orders.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Victrix Mortalis had arranged their armada in a Wall formation. Each ship flying next to the other in a flat line. Wing tip to wing tip. 50 across. 2 ranks deep. One hundred ships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff smiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy behind a Wall formation was simple. Thin your line and stretch out your ships longer than the enemy host. When the center was struck, the sides would pivot like two doors on a hinge towards the middle. Effectively flanking their opponent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its most famous enactment was in the Battle Of Marathon. Where the Athenian army routed and then decimated a superior Persian force. Victrix Mortalis would cast themselves as the Athenians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was as historically significant as it was irrelevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Space battles did not operate under the same conventional limitations as a two-dimensional planet. Space was three-dimensional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff smiled grimly. His fleet was not Persian. They were wolves.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Broadcast my orders across the fleet. Vic Triple-Deck Sleeper formation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Vic formation was a standard aerial combat formation. Three ships. One on point. With two further back on either flank. In this case though, the normal ship placements would be filled by full squadrons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Triple-Deck added two more levels of squadrons. One above and one below. Making the formation three layers high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sleeper squadron flew behind point, nestled among and protected by the other squadrons. It was not a rearguard. It was a special tactics unit. It was meant to harrass the enemy force and make them commit to their plan of attack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“xEEVEEx, take left flank with SCVsUnion and Voxar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel, take right with Librakron and MizzBlaze.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against a wall formation, the flanks would get hit the hardest. He needed their most powerful ships guarding their sides. xEEVEEx was the most battle-hardened and dependable. Machiel was the strongest, but also unpredictable. He was better positioned where he was most likely to hit enemy ships.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sumara and Deathlord291, take top with Ivydocious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seq and Hyten, take bottom with Skinkrules.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Top and bottom squadrons were less likely to receive enemy fire. Sumara, Deathlord291, Seq, and Hyten were brilliant tacticians and expert marksman. They worked best when placed in a superior firing position where they could exact maximum damage. They would help thin the enemy ranks while xEEVEEx and Machiel weathered the brunt of enemy fire.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ArchNadeom, you’re on Sleeper with fritz and Qtarsis.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ArchNadeom and fritz were built like skirmishers. Using hit-and-run tactics, they could engage and harrass larger ships for a significant amount of time until one or the other finally came out on top. Qtarsis would help finish off any stragglers. As a Sleeper squadron, they offered what the fleet would need most from them. Time.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will take point with _sharky_ and CyberWocky.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The strategy of a Vic Triple-Deck Sleeper formation was to hit the opposing force like a wrecking ball. Between the coordinated attack of WarWolff’s twin cannons and _sharky_’s battering ram, there wouldn’t be much left standing after their first frontal assault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They would smash into the enemy ranks with enough power to break through and then keep sailing at maximum speed before the enemy could close on their flanks. It was a tactic that would depend on force and speed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sleeper squadron would drop off like a mine sometime before the two forces collided. Fully exposed and totally outnumbered. Dangling like a delicious red cherry off a fruit tree. Visible, yet just beyond reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tempting target upon which the enemy could redeem themselves after their first battering, while the rest of Wolfpack circled back to enclose on the divided force and now exposed enemy flanks.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Captains, you have fought for this moment. Months in preparation. Tuning your ships. Training your crews. Bloodied. You tested your mettle in battle. For this moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Under the shadow of the S.Q.U.I.D. empire, you grew. Against the incursions of Sushi Train, you banded together. Defying the ravages of war, you endured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A scrabble of ragtag ships, you transformed yourselves into a fleet of a lethal fighting force. Where others fell, you endured. For this moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This moment, you will claim your place in the galaxy. This moment, you will look across the battlefield. You will see the enemy armada assembled against you. And you will say, “No more.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No more will I stand aside. No more will I go unheard. No more will I sit idly by and watch as others tear the galaxy apart. No more will I endure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“From this moment forth, you captains of Wolfpack will face your enemies and you will prevail.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WarWolff looked out upon the mighty warships in formation around him. xEEVEEx in his powerful emerald federation. Sumara in her aqua dorito-shaped squid. _sharky_ with the vicious red teeth painted across his bow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His fleet. His proud captains. The Wolfpack insignia blazened angrily across their hulls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Officers, assemble your squadrons. Wolfpack, prepare to engage.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist014_WarWolff.png&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist014_WarWolff&quot; title=&quot;WarWolff - The Great Wolff&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/20/history-of-the-pack-the-great-wolf.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/20/history-of-the-pack-the-great-wolf.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;13 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;A Farewell&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-246&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #246.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was another goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx summoned us together to announce the parting. Those of us who knew her best. Those of us who would miss her most. Those of us who would feel her absence, no longer flying by our side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl had gone on to Lost Eden.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a galaxy of partings. A captain’s term was not long. A couple months at most. A blazing fiery start full of firepower and fervent friendships sharing a common cause. And then they were gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their ships standing as an empty masoleum of the great war power they had once commanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walking away to disappear in the distant horizon. Good friends departed. Forgotten, but for the glories and friendships they left behind. Those who would remember them most.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl, you only shared one story with me. I was not able to say goodbye. I will do my best to tell your story well:&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;********&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red alarms were flashing across the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl pushed herself up off the console. The display was smashed. She touched her brow. There was a slight cut where her head hit the console. Nothing serious. It could wait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She remembered feeling an internal explosion rupture the ship. Then the shields dropped and they took a volley of enemy fire at full impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She stood and checked on her crew.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cara was slumped against the systems monitor. Test girl grabbed her by the collar and pulled her back in the chair. Her eyes opened slowly with difficulty and then focused on Test girl’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl patted her on the chest, “Cara, bring up the systems and get me a damage report immediately. I need to know what hit us and took out our shields.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jessica was on the floor. The weapons display was destroyed. Jessica took the brunt of it. Test girl didn’t have much hope, but she checked her pulse. Nothing. She squeezed Jessica’s arm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weapons would have to be controlled individually at each of the weapon rooms. She had trained her crew for this. They were good crew. They wouldn’t fail her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, systems report the shield generator was destroyed while the shields were still up. Without the generator, the shields dropped immediately.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generator was destroyed while the shields were up? It couldn’t have been hit by enemy fire. Weapons wouldn’t have gotten through the shields. It must have come from the inside.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cara, patch me through to the shield room.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bridge doors opened and a Trooper walked in. Test girl’s hand dropped to her blaster, then realized it was her Trooper. He looked around bewildered at the disarray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, the comms are destroyed. I can’t reach them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frak. She looked at her Trooper. She only had one runner. She would have to make the message count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cara, fix the communications. I need to be able to talk to my ship. Trooper, head to the teleporter room. Tell Zhang Fei to board the enemy ship and dismantle their shields.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was their only shot. Even the playing field and bring themselves back into the fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trooper looked at her, “Sir, enemy shield generators are heavily guarded. If you send Zhang Fei in there, they’ll kill him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl gave her Trooper a hard look. One crew for many. This was battle. She did not like to be reminded of the lives she risked. Nor would she repeat an order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She gave her Trooper a hard look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yes sir! I will relay your order,” Trooper stood at attention and saluted, then rushed out the door.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Test girl rested her knuckles against the cracked display and leaned against the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She would bring her ship through this. She had to. The lives of her crew depended on her. This new strategm was powerful. One they could use against their enemies. She must relay it to Wolfpack.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;********&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a small vigil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx, WarWolff, Sumara, Caxy, Deathlord291, Machiel, Hyten, Seq and I. Standing together on the captain’s bridge of WarWolff’s great warship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We looked out the observation window. Seeing Test girl’s proud craft in all its glory. Her last flight into Lost Eden. We watched quietly as her ship flew away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;xEEVEEx put his hand against the glass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumara wrapped her arms around his and I placed a hand on his shoulder. Deathlord291 and Machiel bowed their heads. Hyten and Seq lit a candle for their departing friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a tear in WarWolff’s eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only Caxy remained stoic. It was another goodbye. He had said so many before.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodbye, Test girl. May your journey find you happiness and new friendships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodbye, old friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist013_Testgirl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist013_Testgirl&quot; title=&quot;Test girl in Lost Eden&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/08/history-of-the-pack-a-farewell.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/08/history-of-the-pack-a-farewell.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pack History &amp;#35;12 &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Book Of Secrets, pt. 2&amp;#58; The Curse&lt;/i&gt;</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;archnadeom-keeper-of-recordsbrstardate-244&quot;&gt;ArchNadeom, Keeper Of Records.&lt;br /&gt;Stardate #244.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel had been searching for it for years. Finally, here at last. In an unmarked tomb. Buried beneath the S.Q.U.I.D. empire. He had found it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It spoke of battle. It promised of victory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The secrets it held. The knowledge it could reveal. No enemy could withstand him. There was nothing he could not do with the book in his grasp.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel brushed the back of his hand across his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He looked around the room one more time. The cold concrete walls. His Troopers standing at the entrance. The stone pedestal. The thick starlight pouring down through the ceiling. The Book Of Secrets bathed in light atop the slab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He could feel the tension in the air. Himself holding his breath. The excitement. The suspense. Everything he had been pursuing, bringing him to stand here at this one moment in time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel reached out and dipped his fingers in the circle of light. It was like touching a waterfall. He turned his palm upward into the starlight, as it glimmered caressingly around his hand. Like jets of warm water. Splashing through his fingers and down his wrist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It felt of pure energy. Joy. Laughter. Rejuvenation. He couldn’t help but smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was an end to his many years of struggle and pursuit. This rich beautiful starlight running through his fingers. His trophy before him. The Book Of Secrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He would finally lay claim to the treasure for which he had been searching for so long. Machiel turned his hand over and touched its pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circle was broken.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The starlight sucked up into the ceiling. Swallowing the room in darkness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down the hall, in the blacks of the shadows, there was a deep rumbling. A moist coolness oozed into the room from the passageway. Riding on the backs of the waves of a low billowing fog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Troopers backed away from the entrance with their blasters raised. Machiel stepped down from the pedestal, leaving the book behind, and drew his electro-sword. Slowly they converged together in the center of the room. Standing back-to-back. Huddling beneath what little light still came through the ceiling overhead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phosphorescent shapes began to move through the fog. Swimming around the edges. Splashing up and smearing down the walls. Leaving green streaks trailing behind them on the porous concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Menacing, they slowly began circling. Easing towards the center of the room. Circling around Machiel and the Troopers. Weaving between their legs. Sliding up their knees. Finding the soft joints in their armor and oozing in cool fingers.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the Troopers panicked and started firing wildly at the floor and walls. The shots did nothing. It was all Machiel and the other Trooper could do to restrain him. A single bad ricochet in this confined space could kill any one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slowly, the fog and phantasms began pouring up the pedestal and into the book. Dark billows of fog and green phosphorescence oozing between the letters. Seeping into the pages. Staining its bamboo darkly like spilled watercolor.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the last of the fog swept past them and into the book, the cover closed on its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tomb became eerily silent. More frightening than anything they had just witnessed. They were afraid to move lest they disturb the peace of any more otherworldly beings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel carefully walked back to the pedestal, stepping lightly on the balls of his feet. He looked down uncertainly at the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would be a shame to not take it with them. After all the years of searching, despite what they had just seen. There must still be some good in its pages worth salvaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He reached out a hand, then paused. Frowning again uncertainly. Then he grabbed the book and picked it up off the pedestal.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The circular room was empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They walked back down the hallway. Empty. Into the three door room. The middle door still standing open. Just a barren alcove now. Empty. They stepped out onto the bridge. The fluorescent lights were off. The river had stopped running. No shapes swam in its currents. Empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Machiel stepped on the foot of the stairs, he looked back into the tomb. So lifeless now. Whatever dark magic had existed here before, he feared they now carried out with them.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was relieved to exit the archives and climb back onto his ship. He dropped the book on his console and sent his Troopers back to their posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, we’ve got an enemy ship inbound. leoliu86 of S.Q.U.I.D. WarFleet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Release the docking lines and detach from the archives. Shields at full power. Turn the ship 135 degrees to port. Nose up 30 degrees from plane. Thrusters full ahead. Meet them head-on.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well that was quick.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the S.Q.U.I.D. leaders retiring, the rest of the warfleet had disbanded. Seeking refuge among the other alliances. Or starting their own anew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolfpack granted shelter to as many ships as its starports could accomodate. Offering them hospitality and a new place to call home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were the displaced refugees of a fractured empire. In a galaxy torn apart by war.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leoliu86 either refused to accept the disbandment of his fleet. (An alliance he had dedicated his life towards serving.) Was stuck in a pre-programmed automated defense routine. Or was himself looting the coffers of the fallen empire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, he now engaged Machiel in battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ready the weapons for fire. Roborob, prepare boarding parties to target the enemy reactors. Fighter pilots, take out the enemy ACLs. Full power to lasers and missiles.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel opened The Book Of Secrets, “Let’s see what you have for me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A green heatless fire rose up from the pages. Swelling up Machiel’s arms and into the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Power surges started to sound alarms in the laser systems. Arcs of electricity and sparks began popping from the weapons casements. Rippling with a new unknown power they couldn’t quite contain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Open fire! Release that energy build-up before those lasers blow!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His lasers hammered into leoliu86 with enough force to rock the ship. Green fire crackling around the edge of the beams. Punching clear holes in the enemy shields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machiel’s fighters responded immediately and peppered the ship with more gunfire to widen the breaches.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strangely, Machiel’s missle bay 1 started firing EMPs at the enemy reactors. A target that would have zero impact against the enemy ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Missile Bay 1, retarget your EMPs on the enemy lasers. We are not clay pigeon shooting.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Static. Nothing came back over the comms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Missile Bay 1, report.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Static. Still nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Trooper, head to Missle Bay 1 and report back to me with their status.”&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle was over in little more than a minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;leoliu86’s shields were not built to withstand the massive amounts of energy surging from Machiel’s lasers. Once the reactors were distintegrated, his ship became nothing more than a powerless metal bucket floating through space.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, sir? I think you better get down here,” it was Trooper calling from Missile Bay 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battle was a momentous victory, but how Missle Bay 1 had behaved was undismissable. Those EMPs would cost him an arm-and-a-leg to replace. Had it been a stronger enemy, their mistargetting could have cost him the battle. Machiel was not pleased.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He walked into Missle Bay 1, “Report.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh, sir. The missile controls would not respond to our commands. The comms went silent and we couldn’t open the doors. We lost control of the room. The missiles just began firing on their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sir, I hesitate to say this. It was like it had become…. possessed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Book Of Secrets. Machiel remembered the green fire pouring forth from its pages. Up his arms. Into the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What had he brought onboard with them? What had he exposed to his ship and crew?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/archivist/PackHist012_MachielPt2.png&quot; alt=&quot;PackHist012_MachielPt2&quot; title=&quot;Machiel defeats leoliu86&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/06/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://wolfpackpss.github.io/archivist/2016/09/06/history-of-the-pack-the-book-of-secrets-pt2.html</guid>
        
        <category>english</category>
        
        
        <category>archivist</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
